export const questionCategories = {
    "Comptia A+ 1102 test 1": [
        {
          question: "Which Microsoft Windows 10 edition(s) provide(s) the option to join a domain?",
          options: ["Home", "Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
          correctAnswers: ["Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "In Windows 10, Assigned Access is a feature that allows modifying desktop style/user interface by restricting user account access only to a single Windows app (a.k.a. kiosk mode). Windows 10 editions offering this functionality include:",
          options: ["Windows 10 Home", "Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
          correctAnswers: ["Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which edition(s) of Microsoft Windows 10 include(s) the Remote Desktop client component?",
          options: ["Home", "Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
          correctAnswers: ["Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which edition of Windows 10 by default does not include the Remote Desktop server component?",
          options: ["Home", "Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
          correctAnswers: ["Home"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is the physical memory limit for all 32-bit (x86) editions of Windows 10?",
          options: ["2GB", "4GB", "6GB", "8GB"],
          correctAnswers: ["4GB"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "A 64-bit (x64) Windows 10 Home edition provides support for up to:",
          options: ["6GB", "32GB", "64GB", "128GB"],
          correctAnswers: ["128GB"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "What is the physical memory limit for the 64-bit (x64) Windows 10 Pro edition? (In TB)",
          options: ["2TB", "4TB", "6TB", "8TB"],
          correctAnswers: ["2TB"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the 64-bit (x64) Windows 10 editions provide(s) support for up to 6 TB of physical memory?",
          options: ["Windows 10 Home", "Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
          correctAnswers: [ "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which edition(s) of Microsoft Windows 10 include(s) the BitLocker Drive Encryption feature?",
          options: ["Windows 10 Home", "Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
          correctAnswers: ["Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which edition of Windows 10 by default does not include the Local Group Policy Editor (gpedit.msc)?",
          options: ["Home", "Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
          correctAnswers: ["Home"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "An operating system installation type that preserves system settings, personal files, and applications from the older OS version is referred to as an in-place upgrade. Microsoft Windows versions that can be upgraded to Windows 10 via this method include:",
          options: ["Windows XP", "Windows Vista", "Windows 7", "Windows 8.0", "Windows 8.1"],
          correctAnswers: ["Windows 7", "Windows 8.0", "Windows 8.1"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the answers listed below refer to Windows command-line commands used for directory traversal?",
          options: ["cd", "pwd", "dir", "chdir", "path"],
          correctAnswers: ["cd", "chdir"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following Windows Command Prompt commands can be used to list all directory's files and subdirectories contained in the current directory?",
          options: ["dir", "dir /?", "dir * *", "dir /alli", "dir /list"],
          correctAnswers: ["dir"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the answers listed below refer to Windows command-line commands used to create a directory or subdirectory?",
          options: ["md", "mkd", "mdirl", "mkdr", "mkdir"],
          correctAnswers: ["md", "mkdir"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following Windows Command Prompt commands can be used to delete a directory?",
          options: ["rd", "del", "rmdir", "dir /d", "popd"],
          correctAnswers: ["rd", "rmdir"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the Windows command-line commands listed below changes the drive from C: to D:?",
          options: ["C: >D:", "C: >[D:]", "C:\\>D:\\", "C:I>cd D:\\"],
          correctAnswers: ["C:\\>D:\\"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "What is the name of a Windows Command Prompt utility that can be used to display TCP/IP configuration settings?",
          options: ["ifconfig", "nslookup", "ipconfig", "netstat"],
          correctAnswers: ["ipconfig"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "A command-line utility used for checking the reachability of a remote network host is called:",
          options: ["ping", "tracert", "dig", "netstat"],
          correctAnswers: ["ping"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following command-line commands displays the name of the current computer a user is connected to?",
          options: ["host", "hosts", "hostname", "localhost"],
          correctAnswers: ["hostname"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "Netstat is a command-line utility used for:",
          options: ["Displaying active TCP/IP connections", "Testing the reachability of a remote host", "Displaying intermediary points on the packet route", "Viewing the TCP/IP configuration details", "Displaying network protocol statistics"],
          correctAnswers: ["Displaying active TCP/IP connections", "Displaying network protocol statistics"],
          allowMultiple: true
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following Command Prompt utilities in MS Windows allows verifying the file system integrity and fixing logical file system errors?",
          options: ["chkdsk", "StC", "dism"],
          correctAnswers: ["chkdsk"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "Which command-line command in Windows lists a computer's connections to shared resources?",
          options: ["net share", "net use", "net session", "net config"],
          correctAnswers: ["net use"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "Which Command Prompt command in MS Windows lists the user accounts for the computer?",
          options: ["net view", "net session", "net user", "net accounts"],
          correctAnswers: ["net user"],
          allowMultiple: false
        },
        {
          question: "A network command-line utility in MS Windows that tracks and displays the route taken by IP packets on their way to another host is known as:",
          options: ["ping", "traceroute", "nslookup", "tracert"],
          correctAnswers: ["tracert"],
          allowMultiple: false
        }
      ],
     
    "Comptia A+ 1102 test 2": [
       
            {
              question: "For a newly added storage drive, this command-line tool allows you to configure it with a file system enabling Windows to store information on the drive.",
              options: ["gpart", "sfdisk", "mount", "format"],
              correctAnswers: ["format"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the following Command Prompt commands in MS Windows can be used to copy one or more files from one location to another?",
              options: ["copy", "move", "cp.", "pushd"],
              correctAnswers: ["copy"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which Microsoft Windows command-line command(s) allows for copying multiple files and directories, including subdirectories?",
              options: ["xcopy", "move", "robocopy", "copy"],
              correctAnswers: ["xcopy", "robocopy"],
              allowMultiple: true
            },
            {
              question: "Which copying utility accessible via Windows command line interface offers the widest range of options?",
              options: ["move", "robocopy", "copy", "cp"],
              correctAnswers: ["robocopy"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the Command Prompt commands listed below allows for updating multiple Group Policy settings in MS Windows?",
              options: ["net user", "gpupdate", "bcdedit", "gpresult"],
              correctAnswers: ["gpupdate"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "A command-line tool in Windows that displays Group Policy information for a machine or user is called:",
              options: ["gpresult", "net view", "verify", "gpupdate"],
              correctAnswers: ["gpresult"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "The following command can be used to shut down or restart a local or remote host running MS Windows.",
              options: ["poweroff", "exit", "bootcfg", "shutdown"],
              correctAnswers: ["shutdown"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "The sfc Command Prompt utility in MS Windows:",
              options: [
                "Encrypts files and folders",
                "Scans the integrity of all protected system files and replaces incorrect versions with correct Microsoft versions",
                "Displays information about system hardware and software configuration",
                "Checks a disk and displays a status report"
              ],
              correctAnswers: ["Scans the integrity of all protected system files and replaces incorrect versions with correct Microsoft versions"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which command-line commands in Windows can be used to display help information related to a specific utility?",
              options: [
                "[command name] help",
                "man [command name]",
                "[command name] info",
                "help [command name]",
                "[command name] /?"
              ],
              correctAnswers: ["help [command name]", "[command name] /?"],
              allowMultiple: true
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the Command Prompt commands in MS Windows launches a text-based, command-line partitioning utility?",
              options: ["stdisk", "diskutil", "gpart", "diskpart"],
              correctAnswers: ["diskpart"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which network command-line utility in Windows combines the features of ping and tracert?",
              options: ["pathping", "netcfg", "dig", "rpcping"],
              correctAnswers: ["pathping"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the Command Prompt commands in MS Windows launches a pop-up window containing a brief summary of the installed operating system?",
              options: ["winver", "msinfo32", "systeminfo", "msconfig"],
              correctAnswers: ["winver"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which Command Prompt commands in MS Windows move the command-line prompt one folder up in the directory tree (set the prompt at the parent folder of the current folder)?",
              options: ["cd \\", "cd /^", "cd ..", "chdir \\", "chdir /~", "chdir .."],
              // As above, the actual correct commands are "cd .." and "chdir ..". We add "cd .." as the correct answer.
              correctAnswers: ["cd ..", "chdir .."],
              allowMultiple: true
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the Windows command-line commands listed below change the current directory to the root directory?",
              options: ["cd ..", "cd /r", "cd \\", "chdir ..", "chdir /r", "chdir V"],
              // The proper command is "cd \". (Changing to root directory is not the same as moving up one level.)
              correctAnswers: ["cd \\"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the following answers refers to an ipconfig parameter used for displaying the full TCP/IP configuration information for all adapters?",
              options: ["-a", "/?", "/all", "/-al"],
              correctAnswers: ["/all"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the Command Prompt commands listed below are used for resetting the DHCP configuration settings for all adapters in MS Windows?",
              options: ["ipconfig /disable", "ifconfig ethO down", "ipconfig /release", "ipconfig /enable", "ifconfig ethO up", "ipconfig /renew"],
              correctAnswers: ["ipconfig /release", "ipconfig /renew"],
              allowMultiple: true
            },
            {
              question: "Which netstat parameter allows you to display all active TCP connections and the TCP/UDP ports on which the computer is listening?",
              options: ["-a", "-p", "-e", "-r"],
              correctAnswers: ["-a"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "The -b netstat parameter in Microsoft Windows allows you to display the name of an application involved in creating each connection or listening port.",
              options: ["True", "False"],
              correctAnswers: ["True"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the following netstat parameters displays addresses and port numbers in numerical form?",
              options: ["-b", "-n", "-q", "-r"],
              correctAnswers: ["-n"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the command-line tools listed below can be used for troubleshooting DNS-related problems?",
              options: ["arp", "nslookup", "tracert", "pathping"],
              correctAnswers: ["nslookup"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "The /f switch of the chkdsk Command Prompt utility in MS Windows:",
              options: [
                "Locates bad sectors and recovers readable information",
                "Fixes errors on the disk",
                "Displays cleanup messages",
                "Displays the full path and name of every file on the disk"
              ],
              correctAnswers: ["Fixes errors on the disk"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "The /r switch of the chkdsk command-line utility in Windows:",
              options: [
                "Displays cleanup messages",
                "Locates bad sectors and recovers readable information",
                "Uses more system resource to perform a scan as fast as possible",
                "Displays the full path and name of every file on the disk",
                "Fixes errors on the disk"
              ],
              correctAnswers: ["Locates bad sectors and recovers readable information", "Fixes errors on the disk"],
              allowMultiple: true
            },
            {
              question: "Which copy command switch in Windows verifies that the new files are written correctly?",
              options: ["/-y", "/v", "/y", "/a"],
              correctAnswers: ["/v"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the copy command switches suppresses the confirmation prompt displayed when Windows is about to overwrite the contents of an existing file?",
              options: ["Iv", "ly", "/a", "/y"],
              // The documented switch to suppress the confirmation prompt is "/y". None of the provided options exactly match "/y",
              // so we add the actual correct answer.
              correctAnswers: ["/y"],
              allowMultiple: false
            },
            {
              question: "Which of the following is the correct command for setting the time-out period of 30 seconds before powering off a Windows host?",
              options: ["shutdown /r /t 30", "shutdown /s /30", "shutdown /s /t 30", "shutdown /r /30"],
              correctAnswers: ["shutdown /s /t 30"],
              allowMultiple: false
            }
       
         
    ],
//--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

"Comptia A+ 1102 test 3": [
  {
    question: "Which shutdown command switch forces full system shutdown and restart of a Windows host?",
    options: ["-s -r", "/r", "/s r", "-i"],
    correctAnswers: ["/r"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the command-line commands listed below enables a full system shutdown and restart of an MS Windows host after a time-out period of two minutes?",
    options: [
      "shutdown /s /120",
      "shutdown /r /t 120",
      "shutdown /r /120",
      "shutdown /s /t 120"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["shutdown /r /t 120"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which shutdown command switch enables aborting a system shutdown?",
    options: ["/a", "/q", "/e", "/p"],
    correctAnswers: ["/a"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which sfc switch enables a file check that scans integrity of all protected system files and attempts to repair corrupted files?",
    options: ["/scannow", "/verifyonly", "/scanfile", "/verifyfile"],
    correctAnswers: ["/scannow"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Used without any parameters, the help command in MS Windows displays a list of available system commands along with a brief description of each command.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswers: ["True"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "The 'Run as administrator' option in MS Windows available after right-clicking on the Command Prompt application icon enables execution of shell commands reserved for system administrator.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswers: ["True"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following answers describe(s) the function of Task Manager (taskmgr.exe)? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Provides tools for managing network traffic",
      "Allows to close a non-responsive application in Windows",
      "Displays information on programs, processes, and services that are currently running on the computer",
      "Allows to schedule the launch of programs or scripts at pre-defined times or after specified time intervals",
      "In Windows 8 and newer releases of the Microsoft OS, provides access to user applications that can be enabled/disabled during system boot",
      "Allows system administrators to manage the currently logged-in users",
      "Provides real-time reports on how a Windows-based computer is using system resources (CPU/RAM/Disk/Network/GPU usage)"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Allows to close a non-responsive application in Windows",
      "Displays information on programs, processes, and services that are currently running on the computer",
      "Allows system administrators to manage the currently logged-in users",
      "Provides real-time reports on how a Windows-based computer is using system resources (CPU/RAM/Disk/Network/GPU usage)"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Windows Task Manager can be launched by: (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Using the Ctrl+Shift+Esc key combination",
      "Double-clicking on the applet's icon shortcut in the Administrative Tools folder",
      "Pressing Ctrl+Alt+Delete and selecting the Task Manager option from the menu screen",
      "Selecting the Task Manager applet in Windows Control Panel",
      "Right-clicking on the Windows Taskbar and selecting Task Manager",
      "Typing taskmgr (or taskmgr.exe) in the Command Prompt and pressing Enter",
      "Pressing simultaneously the Windows and R keys, typing taskmgr (or taskmgr.exe) in the Run window, and pressing Enter",
      "Right-clicking on the Windows Start button and selecting Task Manager"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Using the Ctrl+Shift+Esc key combination",
      "Pressing Ctrl+Alt+Delete and selecting the Task Manager option from the menu screen",
      "Right-clicking on the Windows Taskbar and selecting Task Manager",
      "Typing taskmgr (or taskmgr.exe) in the Command Prompt and pressing Enter",
      "Pressing simultaneously the Windows and R keys, typing taskmgr (or taskmgr.exe) in the Run window, and pressing Enter",
      "Right-clicking on the Windows Start button and selecting Task Manager"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which tab of the Windows' 10 Task Manager provides an interface for managing background processes?",
    options: ["Processes", "Performance", "Startup", "Users", "Services"],
    correctAnswers: ["Processes"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which Task Manager tab in Windows 10 allows to enable/disable applications that are launched automatically when signing into a user account?",
    options: ["Services", "Startup", "Performance", "Processes", "Users", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswers: ["Startup"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of a Task Manager tab in Windows 10 that provides access to real-time graphs showing total CPU, memory, disk, network, and GPU resource usage?",
    options: ["Services", "Startup", "Performance", "Processes", "Users"],
    correctAnswers: ["Performance"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which Task Manager tab in Windows 10 provides real-time information about system resources used by running applications and background processes?",
    options: ["Processes", "Performance", "Startup", "Users", "Services"],
    correctAnswers: ["Processes"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the answers listed below describes the correct sequence of steps required to close a non-responsive user application in Task Manager in Windows 10?",
    options: [
      "On the App history tab, right-click on the app that isn't responding and select End task (or left-click on the app and use End task button in the bottom right corner of the tab)",
      "On the Performance tab, right-click on the app that isn't responding and select End task (or left-click on the app and use End task button in the bottom right corner of the tab)",
      "On the Processes tab, right-click on the app that isn't responding and select End task (or left-click on the app and use End task button in the bottom right corner of the tab)",
      "On the Applications tab, right-click on the app that isn't responding and select End task (or left-click on the app and use End task button in the bottom right corner of the tab)"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["On the Processes tab, right-click on the app that isn't responding and select End task (or left-click on the app and use End task button in the bottom right corner of the tab)"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "The Task Manager's Users tab in Windows lists all signed-in user accounts along with further details on applications and system resources used by each account. This tab also allows system administrators to close user app, disconnect the user (invoke a Windows lock screen), or to sign them off (force the user to log off).",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswers: ["True"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "A type of customizable framework providing access to a collection of system utilities (in the form of the so-called snap-ins) designed to manage networks, computers, services, and other system components in Microsoft Windows is known as:",
    options: ["PowerShell", "MMC", "Administrative Tools", ".NET"],
    correctAnswers: ["MMC"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Event Viewer (eventvwr.msc) is a Windows administrative utility for monitoring system health and troubleshooting problems with applications, OS, and hardware. Event Viewer allows for browsing and managing event logs. The most common logs available in Event Viewer include Application, System, and Security logs. Depending on the severity of the event, Application and System logs display events that fall into three categories: Information, Warning, and Error. Information events denote normal operation of the system (such as starting and stopping of system services, or successful completion of some routine background tasks), warning events point to non-critical errors (for example when installation of a software component fails because the component is already on the system), error events point to serious issues, for example when programs stop responding and need to be closed by Windows. Security-related events are called audits and inform only about success or failure of an event.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswers: ["True"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following launches a GUI system utility for managing storage media in Windows?",
    options: ["devmgmt.msc", "diskpart.exe", "compmgmt.msc", "diskmgmt.msc"],
    correctAnswers: ["diskmgmt.msc"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the answers listed below refers to a Windows administrative tool providing the capability to schedule the launch of programs or scripts at pre-defined times or after specified time intervals?",
    options: ["taskmgr.exe", "resmon.exe", "taskschd.msc", "perfmon.msc"],
    correctAnswers: ["taskschd.msc"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which Microsoft Windows OS component allows to view and manage installed hardware components and device drivers?",
    options: ["msconfig.exe", "devmgmt.msc", "appwiz.cpl", "compmgmt.msc"],
    correctAnswers: ["devmgmt.msc"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "A Windows Certificate Manager snap-in that allows to view, export, import, and delete digital certificates for the current user is called:",
    options: ["lusrmgr.msc", "certlm.msc", "msconfig.exe", "certmgr.msc"],
    correctAnswers: ["certmgr.msc"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In Microsoft Windows, Local Users and Groups (lusrmgr.msc) is an MMC snap-in for adding/removing users and managing user membership in groups that possess specific rights and permissions on a particular system running MS Windows. The Local Users and Groups utility is included by default in all editions of Windows 10.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswers: ["False"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following administrative tools in MS Windows allows to examine (both in real time and by collecting log data for later analysis) how programs that are run affect a computer's performance?",
    options: ["resmon.exe", "compmgmt.msc", "perfmon.exe", "taskmgr.exe"],
    correctAnswers: ["perfmon.exe"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the tools listed below allows Windows administrators to modify settings that are applied to both users and computers?",
    options: ["msconfig.exe", "gpedit.msc", "lusrmgr.msc", "compmgmt.msc"],
    correctAnswers: ["gpedit.msc"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "A Microsoft Windows application utility used for displaying details about computer's hardware resources, computer components, and software environment is known as:",
    options: ["msconfig.exe", "winver.exe", "msinfo32.exe", "control.exe"],
    correctAnswers: ["msinfo32.exe"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following administrative tools in MS Windows provides a detailed real-time information about hardware resources (CPU, disk, network, and memory) and system resources in use by the OS, services, and running applications?",
    options: ["resmon.exe", "compmgmt.msc", "perfmon.exe", "eventvwr.msc"],
    correctAnswers: ["resmon.exe"],
    allowMultiple: false
  }
],


//--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

"Comptia A+ 1102 test 4": [
  {
    question: "Which of the following answers refers to a Microsoft Windows tool designed for troubleshooting system startup problems?",
    options: ["eventvwr.msc", "sysdm.cpl", "compmgmt.msc", "msconfig.exe"],
    correctAnswers: ["msconfig.exe"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which tab of the System Configuration utility in MS Windows allows to prevent all nonessential applications, services, and device drivers from loading during system startup?",
    options: ["General", "Boot", "Services", "Startup", "Tools"],
    correctAnswers: ["General"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the configuration settings listed below can be managed through the Boot tab of the System Configuration utility in Windows? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Normal/Diagnostic/Selective startup",
      "Default OS to load in a multiboot environment (boot order)",
      "Safe boot options",
      "Boot logging",
      "Amount of hardware resources to be used by the chosen OS in a multiboot environment (e.g., the maximum amount of RAM)",
      "Background applications and processes loaded during system startup",
      "Startup items loaded during system boot"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Default OS to load in a multiboot environment (boot order)",
      "Safe boot options",
      "Boot logging"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "The System Configuration utility tab containing a list of background applications that can be enabled/disabled during Windows system startup is called:",
    options: ["General", "Boot", "Services", "Startup", "Tools"],
    correctAnswers: ["Startup"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In Windows 8 and newer releases of the Microsoft OS, contents of the System Configuration Startup tab can be viewed and managed via:",
    options: ["Task Manager", "Performance Monitor", "Computer Management applet", "Device Manager"],
    correctAnswers: ["Task Manager"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "A Microsoft Windows utility that can be used for freeing up disk space is known as:",
    options: ["cleanmgr.exe", "dfrgui.exe", "compmgmt.msc", "diskmgmt.msc"],
    correctAnswers: ["cleanmgr.exe"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the tools listed below allows to optimize disk performance in MS Windows?",
    options: ["diskmgmt.msc", "cleanmgr.exe", "dfrgui.exe", "compmgmt.msc"],
    correctAnswers: ["dfrgui.exe"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following system utilities in Windows provides access to a database containing system configuration information?",
    options: ["msconfig.exe", "sysdm.cpl", "regedit.exe", "msinfo32.exe"],
    correctAnswers: ["regedit.exe"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "The 'View by Category' option in Microsoft Windows Control Panel allows for displaying entire contents of the Control Panel in a single window enabling quick access to each Control Panel applet.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswers: ["True"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which locations in MS Windows provide access to the Internet Properties (inetcpl.cpl) system utility? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Internet Options applet in Windows Control Panel",
      "Network and Sharing Center applet in Windows Control Panel",
      "Ease of Access applet in Windows Control Panel",
      "Internet Options menu item in Microsoft Edge Tools menu",
      "Windows Run dialog box (after typing in inetcpl.cpl and pressing Enter)",
      "Internet Properties applet in Windows Control Panel"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Internet Options applet in Windows Control Panel",
      "Internet Options menu item in Microsoft Edge Tools menu",
      "Windows Run dialog box (after typing in inetcpl.cpl and pressing Enter)"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which tab of the Windows Internet Properties applet provides an option for deleting temporary Internet files, web browsing history, cookies, saved passwords, and data typed into web forms?",
    options: ["General", "Security", "Privacy", "Content", "Connections", "Programs", "Advanced"],
    correctAnswers: ["General"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "The Security tab of the Internet Properties applet in MS Windows allows to impose restrictions on web content allowed in the built-in web browser.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAnswers: ["True"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "A Windows Internet Properties applet tab containing an option for managing pop-up windows displayed by websites is called:",
    options: ["General", "Security", "Privacy", "Content", "Connections", "Programs", "Advanced"],
    correctAnswers: ["Privacy"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which tab of the Windows Internet Properties applet provides access to advanced cookie management options?",
    options: ["General", "Security", "Privacy", "Content", "Connections", "Programs", "Advanced"],
    correctAnswers: ["Privacy"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the Windows Internet Properties applet tabs listed below allows to manage digital certificates, the AutoComplete functionality, and RSS feeds?",
    options: ["General", "Security", "Privacy", "Content", "Connections", "Programs", "Advanced"],
    correctAnswers: ["Content"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following answers refer to the network configuration options that can be accessed via the Internet Properties applet's Connections tab? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "VPN connection settings",
      "Cookie settings",
      "Proxy server settings",
      "Internet security zone settings",
      "LAN settings"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["VPN connection settings", "Proxy server settings", "LAN settings"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the Windows Internet Properties applet tabs contains an option for managing web browser extensions?",
    options: ["General", "Security", "Privacy", "Content", "Connections", "Programs", "Advanced"],
    correctAnswers: ["Programs"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which tab of the Windows Internet Properties applet provides an option to reset the built-in web browser to its default state (i.e., roll back all the configuration settings to the state they were in when the browser was first installed)?",
    options: ["General", "Security", "Privacy", "Content", "Connections", "Programs", "Advanced"],
    correctAnswers: ["Advanced"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "The Devices and Printers Control Panel applet (control.exe printer) in Windows 10: (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Allows to add/remove wired and wireless devices",
      "Does not offer troubleshooting options",
      "Provides a simplified view of all connected devices",
      "Allows to restore a device driver to the previously installed version",
      "Provides a detailed view of all connected devices",
      "Allows to troubleshoot a device that isn't working properly"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Allows to add/remove wired and wireless devices",
      "Provides a simplified view of all connected devices",
      "Allows to troubleshoot a device that isn't working properly"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "The Programs and Features (appwiz.cpl) Windows Control Panel applet can be used for: (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Uninstalling applications",
      "Conducting repair installation of a malfunctioning program",
      "Adding/removing Windows components",
      "Creating/deleting system restore points",
      "Managing installed updates"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Uninstalling applications",
      "Conducting repair installation of a malfunctioning program",
      "Adding/removing Windows components",
      "Managing installed updates"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "The Network and Sharing Center Control Panel applet (control.exe /name microsoft.networkandsharingcenter) in Windows allows to: (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "View network devices",
      "Manage Web Credentials",
      "View active networks",
      "Set up a new connection or network",
      "Troubleshoot network problems"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "View active networks",
      "Set up a new connection or network",
      "Troubleshoot network problems"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "The Network and Sharing Center Control Panel applet in Windows provides access to: (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Network adapter settings",
      "Advanced sharing settings",
      "Internet security zone settings",
      "Physical location settings",
      "Media streaming options"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Network adapter settings",
      "Advanced sharing settings",
      "Media streaming options"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "The System Control Panel applet (control.exe /name microsoft.system) in MS Windows provides access to basic information about a PC running Microsoft Windows OS. It can be used to view device specifications (such as the CPU model/speed and the amount of installed/usable RAM), as well as Windows specifications (including the currently installed OS edition and its version). The applet also enables quick access to other related system utilities and settings, which, depending on the Windows edition, might include BitLocker settings, remote settings (remote desktop), Device Manager, advanced system settings, system protection (a.k.a. System Restore), and Windows upgrade options. In Windows 10, the contents of the System applet have been moved to a new location and can be displayed in the following ways: (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > System",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > System",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > About menu",
      "Windows Control Panel > Programs and Features > System",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > System"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Start > System",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > About menu",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > System"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following Control Panel applets in Windows 10 provides access to firewall settings (firewall.cpl)?",
    options: ["Windows Firewall", "Internet Options", "Security and Maintenance", "Windows Defender Firewall"],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Defender Firewall"],
    allowMultiple: false
  }
],
//--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

"Comptia A+ 1102 test 5": [
  {
    question: "A Windows Control Panel applet providing access to Microsoft Outlook configuration options is called:",
    options: [
      "Mail",
      "Programs and Features",
      "User Accounts",
      "Administrative Tools"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Mail"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following answers refers to an audio configuration Control Panel applet (mmsys.cpl) in Windows 10?",
    options: [
      "Sound",
      "Device Manager",
      "Sounds and Audio Devices",
      "Computer Management"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Sound"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the Control Panel applets in Windows 10 allows system administrators to modify local user account settings?",
    options: [
      "User Accounts",
      "Local Users and Groups",
      "Security and Maintenance",
      "User Account Control"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Local Users and Groups"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "The Device Manager applet in Windows 10 Control Panel can be accessed via: (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Control Panel (icons view) > Administrative Tools > Device Manager",
      "Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Device Manager",
      "Control Panel (icons view) > Administrative Tools > Computer Management > Device Manager",
      "Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Devices and Printers > Device Manager",
      "Control Panel (icons view) > Device Manager"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Control Panel (icons view) > Administrative Tools > Computer Management > Device Manager",
      "Control Panel (icons view) > Device Manager",
      "Control Panel (icons view) > Administrative Tools > Device Manager"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "A Control Panel applet in Windows 10 designed to speed up the process of finding files is known as:",
    options: [
      "Sync Center",
      "File Explorer Options",
      "Storage Spaces",
      "Indexing Options"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Indexing Options"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "A Windows Control Panel folder containing shortcuts to various system utilities is called:",
    options: [
      "System",
      "Computer Management",
      "Administrative Tools",
      "Security and Maintenance"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Administrative Tools"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the answers listed below refers to a file/folder management applet (control.exe folders) in Windows 10 Control Panel?",
    options: [
      "Folder Options",
      "Windows Explorer",
      "File Explorer Options",
      "Ease of Access Center"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Folder Options"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following key combinations can be used to launch File Explorer (explorer.exe) in Windows?",
    options: [
      "Windows logo key + E",
      "Ctrl + Shift + Esc",
      "Windows logo key + F",
      "Ctrl + Alt + Delete"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows logo key + E"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which sequence of steps in Windows 10 provides access to a configuration setting that enables displaying hidden files, folders, and drives?",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel > Folder Options applet > General tab > Show hidden files, folders, and drives",
      "Windows Control Panel > File Explorer Options applet > View tab > Advanced settings: > Hidden files and folders > Show hidden files, folders, and drives",
      "Windows Control Panel > Folder Options applet > General tab > Advanced settings: > Show hidden files, folders, and drives",
      "Windows Control Panel > File Explorer Options applet > Advanced settings: > Show hidden files, folders, and drives"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Control Panel > File Explorer Options applet > View tab > Advanced settings: > Hidden files and folders > Show hidden files, folders, and drives"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the actions listed below provides access to a Windows 10 File Explorer configuration setting that allows you to show or hide the files and folders that are marked as hidden?",
    options: [
      "Windows logo key + E > View > Hidden items",
      "Windows logo key + F > File > Change folder and search options > Hidden items",
      "Windows logo key + E > View > Advanced settings > Hidden items",
      "Windows logo key + F > File > Show hidden files and folders"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows logo key + E > View > Hidden items"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which sequence of steps in Windows 10 provides access to a configuration setting that allows you to show or hide extensions for known file types?",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel > Folder Options applet > General tab > Hide extensions for known file types",
      "Windows Control Panel > File Explorer Options applet > Advanced settings: > Hidden files and folders > Hide extensions for known file types",
      "Windows Control Panel > Folder Options applet > General tab > Advanced settings: > Hide extensions for known file types",
      "Windows Control Panel > File Explorer Options applet > View tab > Advanced settings: > Hide extensions for known file types"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Control Panel > File Explorer Options applet > View tab > Advanced settings: > Hide extensions for known file types"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following provides access to a Windows 10 File Explorer configuration setting that allows you to show or hide extensions for known file types?",
    options: [
      "Windows logo key + E > View > File name extensions",
      "Windows logo key + F > File > Change folder and search options > File name extensions",
      "Windows logo key + E > View > Options > Advanced settings > File name extensions",
      "Windows logo key + F > File > Settings > File name extensions"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows logo key + E > View > File name extensions"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the settings listed below is NOT part of the General tab of the File Explorer Options applet in Windows 10?",
    options: [
      "Default starting folder after launching File Explorer",
      "Visibility of hidden files, folders, or drives",
      "Folder browsing options (opening each folder in the same window or in its own window)",
      "Opening items (single-click vs. double-click to open an item)",
      "File Explorer browsing history options (Privacy section)"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Visibility of hidden files, folders, or drives"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following answers refer to hibernation mode? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Saves system state (e.g., all open/unsaved files and running applications) on a storage drive",
      "Turns the computer off",
      "System operation can be resumed faster in comparison to sleep mode",
      "Requires small amount of power",
      "Keeps system state (e.g., all open/unsaved files and running applications) in RAM",
      "Resuming system operation from hibernation mode takes longer in comparison to sleep mode"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Saves system state (e.g., all open/unsaved files and running applications) on a storage drive",
      "Turns the computer off",
      "Resuming system operation from hibernation mode takes longer in comparison to sleep mode"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Windows power plan is a collection of hardware and system settings that manages how the computer uses power. In Windows, the power configuration settings can be found in: (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Security and Maintenance > Power Options",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > Power & sleep > Additional power settings",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Power Options",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices > Power & sleep > Additional power settings",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Power Options",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Hardware and Sound > Power Options"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > Power & sleep > Additional power settings",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Power Options",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Power Options"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the answers listed below refer to sleep mode? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Requires small amount of power",
      "Saves system state (e.g., all open/unsaved files and running applications) on a storage drive",
      "Turns the computer off",
      "System operation can be resumed faster in comparison to hibernation mode",
      "Keeps system state (e.g., all open/unsaved files and running applications) in RAM",
      "Resuming system operation from sleep mode takes longer in comparison to hibernation mode"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Requires small amount of power",
      "System operation can be resumed faster in comparison to hibernation mode",
      "Keeps system state (e.g., all open/unsaved files and running applications) in RAM"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "On Windows-based laptops, the Microsoft OS offers an additional power configuration option that allows you to choose what closing the laptop lid does. This setting can be accessed via the following steps: (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices > Power & sleep > Additional power settings > Choose what closing the lid does",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Power Options > Choose what closing the lid does",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Hardware and Sound > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > Choose what closing the lid does",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Power Options > Choose what closing the lid does",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > Power & sleep > Additional power settings > Choose what closing the lid does",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Security and Maintenance > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > Choose what closing the lid does"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Power Options > Choose what closing the lid does",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Power Options > Choose what closing the lid does",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > Power & sleep > Additional power settings > Choose what closing the lid does"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "The fast startup feature in Windows 10 puts a computer into a hibernation state (hybrid shutdown) for a faster resume. Which of the actions listed below provide access to this setting? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices > Power & sleep > Additional power settings > Choose what the power buttons do > Change settings that are currently unavailable > Turn on fast startup",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Power Options > Choose what the power buttons do > Change settings that are currently unavailable > Turn on fast startup",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Hardware and Sound > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > Choose what the power buttons do > Change settings that are currently unavailable > Turn on fast startup",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Power Options > Choose what the power buttons do > Change settings that are currently unavailable > Turn on fast startup",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > Power & sleep > Additional power settings > Choose what the power buttons do > Change settings that are currently unavailable > Turn on fast startup",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Security and Maintenance > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > Choose what the power buttons do > Change settings that are currently unavailable > Turn on fast startup"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Power Options > Choose what the power buttons do > Change settings that are currently unavailable > Turn on fast startup",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Power Options > Choose what the power buttons do > Change settings that are currently unavailable > Turn on fast startup",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > Power & sleep > Additional power settings > Choose what the power buttons do > Change settings that are currently unavailable > Turn on fast startup"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "The Universal Serial Bus (USB) selective suspend is a power saving feature that allows individual USB ports to be suspended when not in use. The USB selective suspend setting in Windows can be accessed via: (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > USB settings > USB selective suspend setting",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > Power & sleep > Additional power settings > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > USB settings > USB selective suspend setting",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > USB settings > USB selective suspend setting",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices > Power & sleep > Additional power settings > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > USB settings > USB selective suspend setting",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Security and Maintenance > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > USB settings > USB selective suspend setting",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Hardware and Sound > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > USB settings > USB selective suspend setting"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > USB settings > USB selective suspend setting",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > Power & sleep > Additional power settings > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > USB settings > USB selective suspend setting",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Power Options > Change plan settings > Change advanced power settings > USB settings > USB selective suspend setting"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following steps provide access to Windows system settings aimed at users with disabilities? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Ease of Access > Ease of Access Center",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Ease of Access Center",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Appearance and Personalization > Ease of Access Center",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Appearance and Personalization > Ease of Access Center",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > Ease of Access Center"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Ease of Access > Ease of Access Center",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Ease of Access Center",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Appearance and Personalization > Ease of Access Center"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the items in Windows 10 Settings app provides access to date, time, region, language, and speech recognition settings?",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > System",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Date and Time",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Clock and Region",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Time & Language"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > Time & Language"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the steps listed below provides access to backup, recovery, and OS upgrade options in the Windows 10 Settings app?",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > System",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Security and Maintenance",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Backup and Restore"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In Windows 10 Settings app, desktop customization settings can be accessed via:",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Personalization",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > Display > Themes",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Appearance and Personalization",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Programs and Features > Turn Windows features on or off"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > Personalization"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following items in Windows 10 Settings app allows you to enable/disable programs that are launched automatically when signing into a user account?",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Accounts > Apps > Startup",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System and Security > Apps > Startup",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Programs and Features > Apps > Startup",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Apps > Startup"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > Apps > Startup"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the items in Windows 10 Settings app allows you to modify OS and application permissions?",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Apps",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Privacy",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Programs and Features"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > Privacy"],
    allowMultiple: false
  }
],

//---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

"Comptia A+ 1102 test 6": [
  {
    question: "Which of the items in Windows 10 Settings app provides access to display, sound, notifications, and power options?",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Hardware and Sound",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Device Manager"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > System"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In Windows 10 Settings app, configuration options for printers, scanners, pointing devices, and Bluetooth can be found in:",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Hardware and Sound",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices and Printers"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > Devices"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which item in Windows 10 Settings app provides access to network configuration options?",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Internet Options",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network and Sharing Center",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network Connections"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In Windows 10 Settings app, Xbox and PC gaming options can be accessed via:",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Apps",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Programs and Features",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Gaming"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > Gaming"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "A Windows 10 Settings app menu that allows to configure connected accounts and sign‐in options is known as:",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > User Accounts",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Local Users and Groups",
      "Windows Start > Settings > User Account Control",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Accounts"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > Accounts"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following statements are true? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Windows-based computers on home networks must be part of a HomeGroup",
      "Windows-based computers on a network must be part of a workgroup or a domain",
      "Windows-based computers on workplace networks are usually part of a domain",
      "Windows-based computers on workplace networks are usually part of a workgroup",
      "Windows-based computers on home networks are usually part of a workgroup",
      "Windows-based computers on home networks are usually part of a domain"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows-based computers on a network must be part of a workgroup or a domain",
      "Windows-based computers on workplace networks are usually part of a domain",
      "Windows-based computers on home networks are usually part of a workgroup"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the statements listed below apply to Windows workgroups? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Security policies and permissions in workgroups are administered centrally",
      "Logging into any computer on a workgroup requires a single account (single sign-on feature)",
      "Workgroups typically consist of no more than twenty computers",
      "There is no limit on the number of hosts that can become a part of a single workgroup",
      "Logging into any computer in a workgroup requires an account on that computer",
      "Each computer in a workgroup has its own security policy"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Workgroups typically consist of no more than twenty computers",
      "Logging into any computer in a workgroup requires an account on that computer",
      "Each computer in a workgroup has its own security policy"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "The configuration settings that allow to change the computer name and domain/workgroup membership in Windows 10 can be accessed via:",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Change... button",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Change... button",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > See the name of this computer > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Change... button",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Change... button",
      "Any of the above steps"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Any of the above steps"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the steps listed below provide(s) access to Windows 10 configuration settings that allow to join a domain or workgroup? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Network ID... button",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > See the name of this computer > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Network ID... button",
      "Windows Start > Settings > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Network ID... button",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Network and Sharing Center > View active networks > click on the Network ID... button",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Network ID... button"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Network ID... button",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > See the name of this computer > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Network ID... button",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > System > About > Rename this PC (advanced) > click on the Network ID... button"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following statements apply to Windows domains? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Logging into any computer on a Windows domain requires a single set of credentials",
      "Security policies and permissions on a Windows domain are administered centrally",
      "Windows domains are based on P2P networking architecture",
      "Each computer on a Windows domain has its own security policy",
      "Windows domains are based on client-server networking architecture",
      "All members of a Windows domain must be on the same local network or subnet"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Logging into any computer on a Windows domain requires a single set of credentials",
      "Security policies and permissions on a Windows domain are administered centrally",
      "Windows domains are based on client-server networking architecture"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following locations/steps allows you to view network shares in Windows?",
    options: [
      "Windows Run dialog box > type in: \\computer name > press Enter (user shares only)",
      "Windows Command Prompt > type in: net share > press Enter (all network shares)",
      "Windows Command Prompt > type in: net view \\computer name > press Enter (user shares only)",
      "Windows Command Prompt > type in: net view \\computer name /all > press Enter (all network shares)",
      "Shared Folders > Shares in the Computer Management utility in Windows Control Panel (all network shares)",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["All of the above"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In Microsoft Windows, the \"$\" sign appended to the end of the name of a network share indicates that the shared folder or drive is:",
    options: [
      "Hidden",
      "Inaccessible",
      "Visible to any user",
      "Encrypted"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Hidden"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the characters listed below indicates that a Windows network share is intended for administrative access?",
    options: [
      "#",
      "$",
      "?",
      "&"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["$"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which sequence(s) of steps in Windows 10 provide(s) access to configuration options that allow you to share a local printer with other PCs on a network? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Devices and Printers > right-click on a selected printer > Printer properties > Sharing tab",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Devices and Printers > right-click on a selected printer > Printer properties > Sharing tab",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices > Printers & scanners > select a printer > Manage > Printer properties > Sharing tab",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > View devices and printers > right-click on a selected printer > Printer properties > Sharing tab",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Devices and Printers > right-click on a selected printer > Properties > Sharing tab"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Devices and Printers > right-click on a selected printer > Printer properties > Sharing tab",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Devices and Printers > right-click on a selected printer > Printer properties > Sharing tab",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices > Printers & scanners > select a printer > Manage > Printer properties > Sharing tab"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following actions in Windows 10 provide(s) access to configuration options for connecting a network printer to a PC (network printer mapping)? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Devices and Printers > Add a printer or scanner > select a printer > Add Device",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Devices and Printers > Add a printer",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices > Printers & scanners > Add printers & scanners > Add a printer or scanner > select a printer > Add Device",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > View devices and printers > Add a printer",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Devices and Printers > Add a printer"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Devices and Printers > Add a printer or scanner > select a printer > Add Device",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > Devices and Printers > Add a printer",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices > Printers & scanners > Add printers & scanners > Add a printer or scanner > select a printer > Add Device"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the actions listed below provide access to a configuration setting that allows you to add a file server component to Windows 10? (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Programs > Turn Windows features on or off > Internet Information Services",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Programs and Features > Turn Windows features on or off > Internet Information Services",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Programs and Features > Turn Windows features on or off > Internet Information Services",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > System > Turn Windows features on or off > Internet Information Services",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Apps > Apps & features > Optional features > More Windows features > Turn Windows features on or off > Internet Information Services"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Programs > Turn Windows features on or off > Internet Information Services",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Programs and Features > Turn Windows features on or off > Internet Information Services",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Apps > Apps & features > Optional features > More Windows features > Turn Windows features on or off > Internet Information Services"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following locations/steps in Windows 10 allows you to create a shortcut to a shared folder or computer on a network?",
    options: [
      "Network and Sharing Center applet in Windows Control Panel",
      "File Explorer > This PC > Computer menu > Map Network drive",
      "Windows Explorer > Computer menu > Map network drive",
      "Shared Folders menu in the Computer Management utility in Windows Control Panel"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["File Explorer > This PC > Computer menu > Map Network drive"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In Windows 10, Windows Defender Firewall can be enabled/disabled via the following steps: (Select 3 answers)",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Internet Options > Security tab > Windows Defender Firewall > Turn Windows Defender Firewall on or off > select network type (Private or Public) > select the Turn on or Turn off Windows Defender Firewall setting",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > Firewall & network protection > select a network profile (Domain network, Private network, or Public network) > under Microsoft Defender Firewall, switch the setting to On or Off",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > Check firewall status > Turn Windows Defender Firewall on or off > select network type (Private or Public) > select the Turn on or Turn off Windows Defender Firewall setting",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > Firewall & network protection > Windows Defender Firewall > Turn Windows Defender Firewall on or off > select network type (Private or Public) > select the Turn on or Turn off Windows Defender Firewall setting",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Windows Defender Firewall > Turn Windows Defender Firewall on or off > select network type (Private or Public) > select the Turn on or Turn off Windows Defender Firewall setting"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > Firewall & network protection > select a network profile (Domain network, Private network, or Public network) > under Microsoft Defender Firewall, switch the setting to On or Off",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > Check firewall status > Turn Windows Defender Firewall on or off > select network type (Private or Public) > select the Turn on or Turn off Windows Defender Firewall setting",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Windows Defender Firewall > Turn Windows Defender Firewall on or off > select network type (Private or Public) > select the Turn on or Turn off Windows Defender Firewall setting"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the steps listed below provide(s) access to an interface that allows you to modify how apps communicate through Windows Defender Firewall? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > Allow an app through Windows Firewall",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > Firewall & network protection > Allow an app through firewall",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Network and Internet > Windows Defender Firewall > Allow an app or feature through Windows Defender Firewall",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet > Windows Firewall > Allow an app through firewall",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Windows Defender Firewall > Allow an app or feature through Windows Defender Firewall"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > Allow an app through Windows Firewall",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > Firewall & network protection > Allow an app through firewall",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Windows Defender Firewall > Allow an app or feature through Windows Defender Firewall"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following Control Panel applets in Windows 10 provides access to the Windows Firewall with Advanced Security tool (wf.msc)?",
    options: [
      "Internet Options > Security tab",
      "Windows Defender Firewall > Advanced settings",
      "Network and Sharing Center",
      "Internet Options > Advanced tab"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Defender Firewall > Advanced settings"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In Windows 10, a firewall interface that allows you to create an exception for a program or port can be accessed via:",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet > Windows Firewall > Advanced settings > right-click on Inbound/Outbound Rules > New Rule...",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > Windows Defender Firewall > Advanced settings > right-click on Inbound/Outbound Rules > New Rule...",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > Firewall & network protection > Advanced settings > right-click on Inbound/Outbound Rules > New Rule...",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Windows Defender Firewall > Advanced settings > right-click on Inbound/Outbound Rules > New Rule...",
      "Any of the above steps"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Any of the above steps"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "A type of logical numeric identifier assigned to every single computer host or other device on a TCP/IP-based network is known as:",
    options: [
      "MAC address",
      "SSID",
      "IP address",
      "Host ID"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["IP address"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the answers listed below refers to a system containing mappings of domain names to various types of data, such as numerical IP addresses?",
    options: [
      "TCP/IP",
      "DNS",
      "SQL",
      "DHCP"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["DNS"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In order to connect to a website and display its contents, a URL entered in the web browser address bar needs to be translated into an IP address. Which of the servers listed below is used to handle this type of request?",
    options: [
      "DNS server",
      "Proxy server",
      "DHCP server",
      "Web server"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["DNS server"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In order to connect to a website and display its contents, a URL entered in the web browser address bar needs to be translated into an IP address. Which of the servers listed below is used to handle this type of request?",
    options: [
      "DNS server",
      "Proxy server",
      "DHCP server",
      "Web server"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["DNS server"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the items in Windows 10 Settings app provides access to display, sound, notifications, and power options?",
    options: [
      "Windows Start > Settings > System",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Devices",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Hardware and Sound",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Device Manager"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Windows Start > Settings > System"],
    allowMultiple: false
  }
],

//-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

"Comptia A+ 1102 test 7": [
  {
    "question": "In a network using subnets, the term \"Default gateway\" refers to a network device (router) that enables exchange of data between hosts residing in different subnets.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a permanent assignment of an IP address?",
    "options": ["Static IP address", "Private IP address", "Dynamic IP address", "Public IP address"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Static IP address"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of server handles the assignment of dynamic IP addresses?",
    "options": ["DHCP server", "Authentication server", "DNS server", "Proxy server"],
    "correctAnswers": ["DHCP server"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refer(s) to data required for manual configuration of network adapter settings in MS Windows? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": ["IP address", "Subnet mask", "Default gateway", "MAC address", "DNS server address", "SSID (a.k.a. network name)"],
    "correctAnswers": ["IP address", "Subnet mask", "Default gateway", "DNS server address"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below describes the correct sequence of steps for accessing the manual configuration interface for IPv4 connections in MS Windows?",
    "options": [
      "Control Panel (category view) > Network and Internet > Network and Sharing Center > Change adapter settings > right-click on the device > select Properties from the pop-up menu > select Internet Protocol version 4 (TCP/IPv4) from the connection components list > click the Properties button > fill in the required fields",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet > select any of the following submenus: Status, Wi-Fi, Ethernet, Dial‐up, VPN, or Mobile hotspot > Change adapter options > right-click on the device > select Properties from the pop‐up menu > select Internet Protocol version 4 (TCP/IPv4) from the connection components list > click the Properties button > fill in the required fields",
      "Control Panel (icon view) > Network and Sharing Center > Change adapter settings > right-click on the device > select Properties from the pop‐up menu > select Internet Protocol version 4 (TCP/IPv4) from the connection components list > click the Properties button > fill in the required fields",
      "Windows Run dialog box > type in: ncpa.cpl + press Enter > right-click on the device > select Properties from the pop‐up menu > select Internet Protocol version 4 (TCP/IPv4) from the connection components list > click the Properties button > fill in the required fields",
      "Right‐click on Windows Start button > select Network Connections > select any of the following submenus: Status, Wi‑Fi, Ethernet, Dial‐up, VPN, or Mobile hotspot > Change adapter options > right‐click on the device > select Properties from the pop‐up menu > select Internet Protocol version 4 (TCP/IPv4) from the connection components list > click the Properties button > fill in the required fields",
      "Right‐click on the Network icon on Windows Taskbar > select Open Network & Internet settings > select any of the following submenus: Status, Wi‑Fi, Ethernet, Dial‐up, VPN, or Mobile hotspot > Change adapter options > right‐click on the device > select Properties from the pop‐up menu > select Internet Protocol version 4 (TCP/IPv4) from the connection components list > click the Properties button > fill in the required fields",
      "Any of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Any of the above"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A system that uses public network (such as the Internet) as a means for creating private encrypted connections between remote locations is referred to as:",
    "options": ["WWAN", "VPN", "PAN", "VLAN"],
    "correctAnswers": ["VPN"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A type of network consisting of computers and peripheral devices that use high‐frequency radio waves to communicate with each other is known as:",
    "options": ["MAN", "WLAN", "LAN", "VLAN"],
    "correctAnswers": ["WLAN"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to the most common network communication technology used in wired LANs, MANs, and WANs?",
    "options": ["Dial‐up", "DSL", "Ethernet", "ISDN"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Ethernet"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which WAN technology takes advantage of cell towers that provide wireless signal coverage for mobile devices?",
    "options": ["PAN", "WWAN", "Satellite", "WLAN"],
    "correctAnswers": ["WWAN"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sequence of steps in Windows 10 provides access to an interface for creating network connections?",
    "options": [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > View network status and tasks > Set up a new connection or network",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet > select any of the following submenus: Status, Wi‑Fi, Ethernet, Dial‐up, VPN, or Mobile hotspot > Network and Sharing Center > Set up a new connection or network",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Internet Options > Connections tab",
      "Right‐click on the Network icon on Windows Taskbar > select Open Network & Internet settings > Network and Sharing Center > Set up a new connection or network",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Network and Sharing Center > Set up a new connection or network",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Network and Internet > Internet Options > Connections tab",
      "Any of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Any of the above"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In computer networking, a computer system or application that acts as an intermediary between another computer and the Internet is commonly referred to as a proxy. In Windows 10, proxy settings can be accessed via: (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Network and Internet > Internet Options > Connections tab > LAN settings > Proxy server",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Proxy",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Internet Options > Connections tab > LAN settings > Proxy server",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet > Proxy",
      "Windows Control Panel > Internet Options > Privacy tab > Advanced > Proxy server"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Network and Internet > Internet Options > Connections tab > LAN settings > Proxy server",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Internet Options > Connections tab > LAN settings > Proxy server",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet > Proxy"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the statements listed below can be used to describe private network setting in Windows? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "The PC remains hidden from other devices on the network",
      "Used for trusted networks, such as home or work networks",
      "The PC can't be used for file and printer sharing",
      "Enables the PC to become discoverable to other devices on the network",
      "Used for untrusted network, such as a WiFi network at a coffee shop",
      "Enables the PC to be used for file and printer sharing"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Used for trusted networks, such as home or work networks",
      "Enables the PC to become discoverable to other devices on the network",
      "Enables the PC to be used for file and printer sharing"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers describe the characteristics of a public network in Windows? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Used for trusted networks, such as home or work networks",
      "Enables the PC to become discoverable to other devices on the network",
      "The PC can't be used for file and printer sharing",
      "Enables the PC to be used for file and printer sharing",
      "Used for untrusted network, such as a WiFi network at a coffee shop",
      "The PC remains hidden from other devices on the network"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "The PC can't be used for file and printer sharing",
      "Used for untrusted network, such as a WiFi network at a coffee shop",
      "The PC remains hidden from other devices on the network"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the steps in Windows 10 provide access to a configuration interface that allows to modify public/private network settings? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > View network status and stats > Change advanced sharing settings",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > select a network profile (Domain network, Private network, or Public network) > Change advanced sharing settings",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Network and Sharing Center > Change advanced sharing settings",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet > select any of the following submenus: Status, Wi‑Fi, Ethernet, Dial‐up, VPN, or Mobile hotspot > Network and Sharing Center > Change advanced sharing settings",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > Check firewall status > unfold Private/Public networks menu > modify network settings",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Windows Defender Firewall > unfold Private/Public networks menu > modify network settings"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Network and Sharing Center > Change advanced sharing settings",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Network & Internet > select any of the following submenus: Status, Wi‑Fi, Ethernet, Dial‐up, VPN, or Mobile hotspot > Network and Sharing Center > Change advanced sharing settings",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Windows Defender Firewall > unfold Private/Public networks menu > modify network settings"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "In Windows 10, the path to a network drive can be located in File Explorer (explorer.exe). After selecting \"This PC\" item from the left hand menu, the path should be visible in the address bar after double clicking on the drive's icon.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["False"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A Windows 10 feature that allows to impose data limit on an Internet connection to save bandwidth is called:",
    "options": ["Measured service", "Bandwidth cap", "Resource pooling", "Metered connection"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Metered connection"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the statements listed below is true?",
    "options": [
      "A 32-bit hardware provides support for both 32-bit and 64-bit OSs and applications",
      "A computer with a 32-bit CPU can run 64-bit OSs and applications without compatibility issues",
      "A 64-bit hardware provides support only for 64-bit OSs and applications",
      "A computer with a 64-bit CPU can run most 32-bit OSs and applications without compatibility issues"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["A computer with a 64-bit CPU can run most 32-bit OSs and applications without compatibility issues"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which built-in functionality allows certain CPU models to take over tasks normally executed by a more powerful, dedicated graphics controller?",
    "options": ["VGA mode", "Integrated GPU", "Multicore architecture", "Hyper-threading"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Integrated GPU"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A special-purpose memory used by graphics controllers is referred to as:",
    "options": ["SRAM", "PROM", "VRAM", "DRAM"],
    "correctAnswers": ["VRAM"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A 32-bit system typically provides support for up to:",
    "options": ["4 GB of RAM", "8 GB of RAM", "16 GB of RAM", "32 GB of RAM"],
    "correctAnswers": ["4 GB of RAM"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the theoretical limit of addressable RAM for a 64-bit CPU?",
    "options": ["64 GB", "128 GB", "2 TB", "6 TB", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswers": ["None of the above"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following terms denotes a 32-bit CPU architecture?",
    "options": ["x32", "x48", "x64", "x86"],
    "correctAnswers": ["x86"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to 64-bit CPU architecture?",
    "options": ["x32", "x48", "x64", "x86"],
    "correctAnswers": ["x64"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The presence of the Program Files (x86) folder on the C drive in MS Windows indicates that the PC takes advantage of 32-bit architecture and OS version.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["False"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In computer security, a type of small-factor physical device used for authentication is commonly referred to as a hardware token.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A 64-bit (x64) Windows 10 Home edition provides support for up to:",
    "options": ["6GB", "32GB", "64GB", "128GB"],
    "correctAnswers": ["128GB"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the physical memory limit for the 64-bit (x64) Windows 10 Pro edition? (In TB)",
    "options": ["2TB", "4TB", "6TB", "8TB"],
    "correctAnswers": ["2TB"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the 64-bit (x64) Windows 10 editions provide(s) support for up to 6 TB of physical memory?",
    "options": ["Windows 10 Home", "Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which edition(s) of Microsoft Windows 10 include(s) the BitLocker Drive Encryption feature?",
    "options": ["Windows 10 Home", "Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which edition of Windows 10 by default does not include the Local Group Policy Editor (gpedit.msc)?",
    "options": ["Home", "Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Home"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],
//-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

"Comptia A+ 1102 test 8":[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following commands are valid for directory traversal in Unix-like systems? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": ["cd", "chdir", "pwd", "ls"],
    "correctAnswers": ["cd", "chdir"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following commands are used for file manipulation in Unix-like systems? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": ["cp", "mv", "rm", "grep"],
    "correctAnswers": ["cp", "mv", "rm"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you display hidden files on a Windows computer?",
    "options": [
      "Open Control Panel → File Explorer Options → View tab → Show hidden files and folders",
      "Use Diskpart to list hidden files",
      "Run msinfo and filter for hidden attributes",
      "Right-click on the desktop and select 'Show hidden files'"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Open Control Panel → File Explorer Options → View tab → Show hidden files and folders"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are true about the taskkill command? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": [
      "It can terminate a process using its process ID with the /pid option.",
      "It can terminate a process using its image name with the /im option.",
      "It can terminate all child processes using the /t option.",
      "It lists all services running within each process."
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "It can terminate a process using its process ID with the /pid option.",
      "It can terminate a process using its image name with the /im option.",
      "It can terminate all child processes using the /t option."
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are examples of hardware tokens? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": ["Cable lock", "Key fob", "Biometric reader", "Passphrase", "Smart card"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Key fob", "Smart card"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "If an application written for an earlier version of MS Windows doesn't run correctly, the compatibility mode settings in Windows 10 can be changed manually by right-clicking on the program icon and:",
    "options": [
      "Selecting \"Compatibility mode\" option from the pop-up menu > applying the required settings",
      "Choosing \"Restore previous versions\" option from the pop-up menu > applying the required settings on the Compatibility tab",
      "Selecting \"Run program using recommended compatibility settings\" option from the pop-up menu",
      "Clicking on the Properties menu item > applying the required settings on the Compatibility tab"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Clicking on the Properties menu item > applying the required settings on the Compatibility tab"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a type of file containing an exact copy of the contents of an optical disc?",
    "options": ["Swap file", "Master image", "Snapshot file", "ISO image", "Shadow copy"],
    "correctAnswers": ["ISO image"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to application distribution methods?",
    "options": [
      "Optical storage media (CD/DVD/Blu-Ray)",
      "USB flash drives",
      "Network downloads",
      "ISO images",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["All of the above"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the statements listed below describe the characteristic features of open-source applications and OSs? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Proprietary software",
      "Permission to modify and redistribute the application",
      "Free access to the application code",
      "Permission to use the application only under certain conditions",
      "Lack of free access to the application code"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Permission to modify and redistribute the application",
      "Free access to the application code"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are not examples of proprietary software? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": ["MS Windows", "macOS", "Linux", "iOS", "Android"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Linux", "Android"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer(s) to the characteristics of macOS? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": [
      "Developed by Microsoft",
      "Designed for tablets",
      "Developed by Apple",
      "Designed for laptops",
      "Developed by Google",
      "Designed for desktops"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Developed by Apple", "Designed for laptops", "Designed for desktops"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of a lightweight operating system designed by Google for small-factor PCs, laptops, tablets, and mobile devices?",
    "options": ["iOS", "macOS", "Android", "Chrome OS"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Chrome OS"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to an OS that uses web browser as its main user interface?",
    "options": ["Linux", "Chrome OS", "MS Windows", "macOS"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Chrome OS"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer to the characteristics of iPadOS? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Developed by Apple",
      "Designed for workstations",
      "Developed by Google",
      "Designed for smartphones",
      "Developed by Microsoft",
      "Designed for tablets"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Developed by Apple", "Designed for tablets"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "An Apple-proprietary OS designed for tablets, smartphones and mobile devices is called:",
    "options": ["macOS", "Android", "iOS", "Chrome OS"],
    "correctAnswers": ["iOS"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to an open-source mobile OS designed by Google for smartphones and tablets?",
    "options": ["Windows", "Android", "iOS", "Chrome OS"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Android"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Examples of workstation OSs include: (Select all that apply)",
    "options": ["macOS", "Windows", "Linux", "Android", "iOS", "iPadOS", "Chrome OS"],
    "correctAnswers": ["macOS", "Windows", "Linux"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer to OSs used in smartphones and tablets? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": ["macOS", "Chrome OS", "iOS", "Android", "iPadOS"],
    "correctAnswers": ["iOS", "Android", "iPadOS"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refer(s) to (a) file system type(s) specific to Microsoft Windows OSs? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": ["NTFS", "ext3", "FAT32", "ext4", "APFS", "exFAT"],
    "correctAnswers": ["NTFS", "FAT32", "exFAT"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "The 4 GB maximum file size limit and 2 TB maximum volume size limit are the characteristic features of:",
    "options": ["NTFS", "FAT32", "NFS", "exFAT"],
    "correctAnswers": ["FAT32"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The advantages of the NTFS over FAT32 file system include:",
    "options": [
      "Disk quotas",
      "Compression",
      "Increased file size limit",
      "Object permissions",
      "Encryption",
      "All of the above features are improvements implemented in NTFS not available in FAT32"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["All of the above features are improvements implemented in NTFS not available in FAT32"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "ext3 and ext4 are examples of default file systems used by:",
    "options": ["iOS", "macOS", "Windows Server", "Linux distributions"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Linux distributions"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a file system developed by Apple for its operating systems?",
    "options": ["APFS", "FAT", "NTFS", "exFAT"],
    "correctAnswers": ["APFS"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A Microsoft-proprietary file system optimized for flash drives is known as:",
    "options": ["ext3", "FAT32", "NFS", "exFAT", "APFS"],
    "correctAnswers": ["exFAT"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following terms refers to a product/service that no longer receives continuing support?",
    "options": ["EOF", "ERP", "EOL", "ETL"],
    "correctAnswers": ["EOL"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "An operating system cross-platform compatibility feature allows certain types of data files created on one type of OS to be seamlessly read and modified on a different OS type.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "All modern applications are designed as cross-platform software which allows them to be run on different operating systems (e.g., Windows, Linux, or macOS) without any modifications in the application source code.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["False"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the OS boot methods listed below takes advantage of a network interface?",
    "options": ["CD-ROM/DVD/Blu-ray", "USB", "eSata", "PXE", "HDD/SSD", "Disk partition"],
    "correctAnswers": ["PXE"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],
//---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 9":[
  {
    "question": "What is the name of an operating system installation type that preserves system settings, personal files, and applications from the older OS version?",
    "options": [
      "Clean install",
      "In-place upgrade",
      "Unattended installation",
      "Image deployment"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["In-place upgrade"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following replaced removable media used for reformatting storage drives and restoring an operating system to the original factory condition?",
    "options": [
      "Primary partition",
      "Extended partition",
      "System partition",
      "Recovery partition"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Recovery partition"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A type of Windows installation that erases the entire contents of a target partition is called:",
    "options": [
      "Refresh",
      "Clean install",
      "In-place upgrade",
      "Repair installation"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Clean install"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the installation types listed below provides a simpler and less costly alternative to manual OS installation in an environment consisting of multiple hosts requiring the same configuration settings?",
    "options": [
      "In-place upgrade",
      "Remote network installation",
      "Image deployment",
      "Unattended installation"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Image deployment"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Windows repair installation: (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Modifies application configuration settings",
      "Does not affect user applications",
      "Removes user files",
      "Preserves application configuration settings",
      "Removes user applications",
      "Does not affect user files"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Does not affect user applications",
      "Preserves application configuration settings",
      "Does not affect user files"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following enable installation of an OS via network interface? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "GPT",
      "diskpart",
      "Netboot",
      "PXE",
      "gpupdate"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Netboot",
      "PXE"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Devices that are not detected during the operating system installation process might require loading alternate third-party drivers.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the sources listed below allow for obtaining, installing, and updating device drivers used by Microsoft Windows OSs? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Windows Update",
      "Computer Management utility",
      "Device manufacturer",
      "Microsoft Store",
      "Windows Device Manager utility"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Windows Update",
      "Device manufacturer",
      "Microsoft Store"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the advantages of organizing storage drive space into multiple partitions? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Multiboot environment",
      "Separated disk space used for virtual memory",
      "Preventative measure against drive failures",
      "Separation of user files from the operating system and application files",
      "Increased overall disk storage space available for user data"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Multiboot environment",
      "Separated disk space used for virtual memory",
      "Separation of user files from the operating system and application files"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a unique string of characters used to identify hardware, software, and data?",
    "options": [
      "OID",
      "GUID",
      "URI",
      "OUI"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["GUID"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below describe the characteristics of the MBR partition style? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Legacy BIOS",
      "Up 128 primary partitions",
      "Maximum disk size limit of 2 TB",
      "Overall number of partitions limited to 4",
      "Support for disks larger than 2 TB",
      "UEFI BIOS"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Legacy BIOS",
      "Maximum disk size limit of 2 TB",
      "Overall number of partitions limited to 4"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refer to GPT? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Support for disks larger than 2 TB",
      "Overall number of partitions limited to 4",
      "Legacy BIOS",
      "Up 128 primary partitions",
      "UEFI BIOS",
      "Maximum disk size limit of 2 TB"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Support for disks larger than 2 TB",
      "Up 128 primary partitions",
      "UEFI BIOS"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "In GPT disk architecture, each partition is labeled with a unique identifier known as GUID.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Quick format: (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Does not erase data",
      "Requires more time than full format",
      "Checks the drive for bad sectors",
      "Erases all data to prevent its recovery",
      "Does not check the drive for bad sectors",
      "Requires less time than full format"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Does not erase data",
      "Does not check the drive for bad sectors",
      "Requires less time than full format"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Full format: (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Does not check the drive for bad sectors",
      "Requires less time than quick format",
      "Erases all data to prevent its recovery",
      "Requires more time than quick format",
      "Does not erase data",
      "Checks the drive for bad sectors"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Erases all data to prevent its recovery",
      "Requires more time than quick format",
      "Checks the drive for bad sectors"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "A list of computer hardware proven to be compatible with a particular OS is referred to as:",
    "options": [
      "CRL",
      "HCL",
      "PRL",
      "HAL"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["HCL"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a file extension used in macOS for a file that contains an exact copy of the contents of a storage device?",
    "options": [
      ".dmg",
      ".pkg",
      ".app",
      ".pfx"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [".dmg"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a macOS application installer file?",
    "options": [
      ".exe",
      ".app",
      ".pkg",
      ".dmg"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [".pkg"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which location in macOS provides access to application updates menu?",
    "options": [
      "Explorer",
      "App Store",
      "iCloud",
      "Spotlight"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["App Store"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "An application in macOS can be executed by double-clicking on an icon with .app file extension. The icon with the .app extension also points to a directory (a.k.a. application bundle) that contains all the files necessary to run the application. Contents of the directory can be examined by right-clicking on the application's icon and selecting Show Package Contents from the context menu. The process of uninstalling macOS applications that store all files in one place is simplified and relies on moving the program icon to the system recycle bin (called Trash).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an SSO solution for all Apple's products and services?",
    "options": [
      "Secure Enclave",
      "Apple ID",
      "Sign in with Apple",
      "Gatekeeper"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Apple ID"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Managed Apple ID is an account management solution that allows system administrators to disable certain features of Apple devices used by employees in a business environment.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following macOS features allows to create switchable desktop environments?",
    "options": [
      "Spaces",
      "Personalization",
      "Display",
      "Aero"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Spaces"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Time Machine is a built-in backup utility for:",
    "options": [
      "Linux",
      "macOS",
      "Windows",
      "Other"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["macOS"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A macOS system feature providing single-screen thumbnail preview of all open windows and applications is known as:",
    "options": [
      "Spotlight",
      "Mission Control",
      "Screen Sharing",
      "Desktop Window Manager"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Mission Control"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],
//--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 10":[
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a macOS password management system?",
    "options": [
      "Kerberos",
      "Credential Manager",
      "BitLocker",
      "Keychain"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Keychain"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a macOS system search utility?",
    "options": [
      "Explorer",
      "File explorer",
      "Spotlight",
      "Finder"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Spotlight"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A service that enables storage of data on Apple cloud servers is called:",
    "options": [
      "iCloud",
      "Remote Disk",
      "OneDrive",
      "Dropbox"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["iCloud"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following locations in macOS provide access to multi-touch interface settings (a.k.a. Gestures)? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Apple menu > System Preferences... > Mouse",
      "Apple menu > App Store... > Categories > Devices > Trackpad",
      "Apple menu > System Preferences... > Devices > Mouse",
      "Apple menu > System Preferences... > Trackpad",
      "Apple menu > App Store... > Categories > Devices > Mouse",
      "Apple menu > System Preferences... > Devices > Trackpad"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Apple menu > System Preferences... > Mouse",
      "Apple menu > System Preferences... > Trackpad"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a macOS file manager application?",
    "options": [
      "Konqueror",
      "Explorer",
      "Finder",
      "Nautilus"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Finder"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the macOS features enables access to optical drive of another computer over a network?",
    "options": [
      "Disk Utility",
      "Remote Desktop",
      "Explorer",
      "Remote Disc"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Remote Disc"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of a macOS equivalent of Windows Taskbar?",
    "options": [
      "Explorer",
      "Dock",
      "Spotlight",
      "Finder"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Dock"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a macOS disk maintenance tool?",
    "options": [
      "Disk Cleanup",
      "Disk Management",
      "chkdsk",
      "Disk Utility"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Disk Utility"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a disk encryption utility in macOS?",
    "options": [
      "FileVault",
      "TrueCrypt",
      "Disk Utility",
      "BitLocker"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["FileVault"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following system utilities in macOS provides access to different command-line shells?",
    "options": [
      "command.com",
      "Terminal",
      "cmd.exe",
      "PowerShell"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Terminal"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "An unresponsive application/process in macOS can be terminated with the use of:",
    "options": [
      "shutdown command",
      "Alt + F4 key combination",
      "taskkill command",
      "Force Quit"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Force Quit"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Linux command allows to display information about files and directories contained within the current working directory?",
    "options": [
      "pwd",
      "ls",
      "grep",
      "ps"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["ls"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A Linux command displaying an absolute path to (i.e., full filename of) the current working directory is called:",
    "options": [
      "mv",
      "pwd",
      "rm",
      "dir"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["pwd"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Linux command-line command is used for transferring files/directories to a different directory?",
    "options": [
      "replace",
      "export",
      "move",
      "mv"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["mv"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the Linux command used for renaming files and directories?",
    "options": [
      "rm",
      "ps",
      "mv",
      "ls"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["mv"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Linux commands listed below allows for copying files and directories?",
    "options": [
      "cp",
      "copy",
      "xcopy",
      "robocopy"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["cp"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A command-line command in Linux used for deleting files and directories is known as:",
    "options": [
      "erase",
      "rm",
      "del",
      "edit"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["rm"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the function of the Linux chmod command?",
    "options": [
      "Changes file access permissions",
      "Changes file owner and group permissions",
      "Compares the contents of two files or sets of files",
      "Changes the Linux command prompt"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Changes file access permissions"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the function of the Linux chown command?",
    "options": [
      "Changes the Linux command prompt",
      "Compares the contents of two files or sets of files",
      "Changes file owner and group permissions",
      "Changes file access permissions"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Changes file owner and group permissions"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a Linux command that allows to assume the identity of a different system user and execute commands with security privileges of that user account?",
    "options": [
      "sync",
      "id",
      "usermod",
      "su"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["su"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A Linux command that temporarily modifies security privileges to allow an execution of a single command that requires root access permissions is called:",
    "options": [
      "id",
      "sudo",
      "usermod",
      "su"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["sudo"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of a command-line utility used for managing (i.e., finding, installing, or updating) software packages on Debian and Debian-based Linux distributions?",
    "options": [
      "rpm",
      "dpkg",
      "yum",
      "apt-get"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["apt-get"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a package management utility used on Red Hat and Red Hat-based Linux distributions?",
    "options": [
      "dpkg",
      "Synaptic",
      "yum",
      "apt-get"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["yum"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a Linux command-line utility used for configuring network interfaces?",
    "options": [
      "ip",
      "net config",
      "ipconfig",
      "networksetup"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["ip"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Linux commands listed below can be used to display the amount of available disk space?",
    "options": [
      "diskpart",
      "df",
      "chkdsk",
      "diskutil"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["df"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],
//-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 11":[
  {
    "question": "A Linux command-line command that enables searching files for lines containing a match to a given text pattern is known as:",
    "options": [
      "rm",
      "chmod",
      "find",
      "grep"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["grep"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of a Linux command-line utility used for displaying a snapshot of running processes?",
    "options": [
      "ps",
      "tasklist",
      "nbtstat",
      "id"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["ps"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following commands in Linux can be used to display help information related to a specific command-line command/utility?",
    "options": [
      "[command name] help",
      "man [command name]",
      "[command name] info",
      "help [command name]",
      "[command name] /?"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["man [command name]"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Linux command-line utility provides a functionality similar to Windows Task Manager?",
    "options": [
      "tasklist",
      "iostat",
      "top",
      "Get-Process"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["top"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Linux utilities listed below can be used to display real-time system resources utilization statistics?",
    "options": [
      "taskmgr",
      "top",
      "nbtstat",
      "tasklist"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["top"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A Linux command-line utility used to search for files and directories is called:",
    "options": [
      "find",
      "path",
      "search",
      "grep"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["find"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a Linux network administration command-line utility used for DNS queries?",
    "options": [
      "ping",
      "tracert",
      "dig",
      "pathping"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["dig"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A Linux command that allows to create, view, and concatenate files is known as:",
    "options": [
      "echo",
      "concat",
      "printf",
      "cat"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["cat"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a Linux command-line text editor?",
    "options": [
      "nano",
      "gVim",
      "Notepad",
      "gedit"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["nano"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following Linux utilities can be used for creating backups?",
    "options": [
      "dd",
      "cpio",
      "rsync",
      "tar",
      "dump",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["All of the above"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the characteristic features of SMB/CIFS? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": [
      "Used mainly by computers running Linux distributions",
      "Provides shared access to files, directories, and devices",
      "Used mainly by computers running Microsoft Windows operating systems",
      "Enables voice and multimedia communications over IP networks"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Provides shared access to files, directories, and devices",
      "Used mainly by computers running Microsoft Windows operating systems"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Samba? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": [
      "Cross-platform printer sharing solution",
      "Open-source implementation of CIFS",
      "Linux web server software",
      "Cross-platform network file sharing solution",
      "Open-source implementation of SMB"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Cross-platform printer sharing solution",
      "Open-source implementation of CIFS",
      "Cross-platform network file sharing solution",
      "Open-source implementation of SMB"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "An access control vestibule (a.k.a. mantrap) is a physical security access control system used to prevent unauthorized users from gaining access to restricted areas. An example mantrap could be a two-door entrance point connected to a guard station wherein a person entering the mantrap from the outside remains locked inside until he/she provides an authentication token required to unlock the inner door.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer(s) to (an) example(s) of physical security token(s)? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": [
      "ACL",
      "RFID badge",
      "Key fob",
      "PIN",
      "Smart card"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "RFID badge",
      "Key fob",
      "Smart card"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "In computer security, the term \"Biometrics\" refers to physical characteristics of the human body that can be used for identification and access control purposes.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Examples of biometric devices include: (Select all that apply)",
    "options": [
      "OCR scanner",
      "Retina scanner",
      "ICR scanner",
      "Fingerprint scanner",
      "Palmprint scanner"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Retina scanner",
      "Fingerprint scanner",
      "Palmprint scanner"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "In the context of physical security, a magnetometer is a device used for detecting metal objects.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A security rule that prevents users from accessing information and resources that lie beyond the scope of their responsibilities is known as the principle of least privilege.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following acronyms refers to a set of rules that specify which users or system processes are granted access to objects as well as what operations are allowed on a given object?",
    "options": [
      "CRL",
      "NAT",
      "BCP",
      "ACL"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["ACL"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A rule-based access control mechanism implemented on routers, switches, and firewalls is referred to as:",
    "options": [
      "ACL",
      "CSR",
      "DLP",
      "AUP"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["ACL"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Authentication process can be based on various categories of authentication factors and attributes. Multifactor authentication systems require implementation of authentication factors from two or more distinct categories.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the examples listed below meets the requirement of multifactor authentication?",
    "options": [
      "Password and biometric scan",
      "Username and PIN",
      "Smart card and ID badge",
      "Voice recognition and fingerprint scan"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Password and biometric scan"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of a soft authentication token?",
    "options": [
      "Key fob",
      "USB token",
      "Authenticator app",
      "Smart card"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Authenticator app"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of software enables a centralized administration of mobile devices?",
    "options": [
      "MFA",
      "MMC",
      "MDM",
      "MFD"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["MDM"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a solution that facilitates the enforcement of mobile device policies and procedures?",
    "options": [
      "MFA",
      "MMC",
      "MDM",
      "MFD"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["MDM"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],
//------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 12":[
  {
    "question": "A type of hierarchical database structure used in Windows Server environments that enables centralized management of devices and resources on a network is known as:",
    "options": [
      "HomeGroup",
      "Active Directory",
      "Workgroup",
      "Windows domain"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Active Directory"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "On a Windows domain, this tool can be used by system administrators to configure initial desktop environment (which may include mapping a network drive or setting up access to a shared printer) for a specific user.",
    "options": [
      "MDM policy",
      "Login script",
      "Group Policy",
      "Directory permissions"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Login script"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following terms describes a large network of Windows-based PCs under single administration?",
    "options": [
      "HomeGroup",
      "Windows domain",
      "Active Directory",
      "Workgroup"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Windows domain"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In Windows Active Directory environment, this feature enables centralized management and configuration of operating systems, applications, and user account settings.",
    "options": [
      "Local Users and Groups",
      "Resource Monitor",
      "Group Policy",
      "User Account Control (UAC)"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Group Policy"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Windows Active Directory service allows for grouping users and computers into containers known as Organizational Units (OUs). An OU is the smallest unit to which system administrators can assign Group Policy settings to manage the configuration and use of accounts and resources within a given OU.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In Windows domain environment, the term \"Home Folder\" refers to a directory on a local PC where users can back up their data and files.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["False"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the Windows Active Directory Group Policy settings allows network administrators to map a folder on a user's PC to a server-based location?",
    "options": [
      "Folder redirection",
      "Local Users and Groups",
      "User Account Control (UAC)",
      "Directory permissions"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Folder redirection"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In Windows Active Directory environment, this feature can be used by system administrators to assign user rights and grant permissions to shared resources.",
    "options": [
      "Global groups",
      "Security Groups",
      "Distribution Groups",
      "Universal groups"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Security Groups"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which wireless encryption scheme offers the highest level of protection?",
    "options": [
      "WEP",
      "WPA3",
      "WPS",
      "WPA",
      "WPA2"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["WPA3"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a security protocol designed to strengthen WEP implementations?",
    "options": [
      "PEAP",
      "TKIP",
      "CCMP",
      "WPA2"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["TKIP"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following wireless technologies has been deprecated and should not be used due to its known vulnerabilities?",
    "options": [
      "EAP",
      "WPA2",
      "AES",
      "WEP"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["WEP"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the cryptographic algorithms listed below is the least vulnerable to attacks?",
    "options": [
      "AES",
      "DES",
      "RC4",
      "3DES"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["AES"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following encryption schemes is used in WiFi Protected Access 2 (WPA2)?",
    "options": [
      "RC4",
      "AES-CCMP",
      "TKIP with RC4",
      "AES-GCMP"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["AES-CCMP"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "For the purpose of encryption, WiFi Protected Access 3 (WPA3) takes advantage of: (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "AES-GCMP",
      "PSK",
      "TKIP with RC4",
      "RC4",
      "AES-CCMP",
      "SAE"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["AES-GCMP", "SAE"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following acronyms refers to a client authentication method used in WPA2 Personal mode?",
    "options": [
      "AES",
      "RC4",
      "IKE",
      "PSK",
      "SAE"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["PSK"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the acronyms listed below refers to a client authentication method used in WPA3 Personal mode?",
    "options": [
      "SAE",
      "IKE",
      "RC4",
      "PSK",
      "AES"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["SAE"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following would be the best solution for securing a small network that lacks an authentication server?",
    "options": [
      "WPA3-SAE",
      "WPA2-Enterprise",
      "WPA2-PSK",
      "WPA3-Enterprise"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["WPA3-SAE"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the characteristic features of WPA2/WPA3 Enterprise mode? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Suitable for large corporate networks",
      "IEEE 802.1D",
      "Does not require an authentication server",
      "IEEE 802.1X",
      "Suitable for all types of wireless LANs",
      "Requires RADIUS authentication server"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Suitable for large corporate networks",
      "IEEE 802.1X",
      "Requires RADIUS authentication server"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which part of the AAA security architecture deals with the verification of the identity of a person or process?",
    "options": [
      "Authentication",
      "Authorization",
      "Accounting"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Authentication"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to the process of granting or denying access to resources?",
    "options": [
      "Authentication",
      "Authorization",
      "Accounting"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Authorization"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In the AAA security architecture, the process of tracking accessed services as well as the amount of consumed resources is called:",
    "options": [
      "Authentication",
      "Authorization",
      "Accounting"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Accounting"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Examples of more complex authentication protocols providing the AAA functionality include: (Select all that apply)",
    "options": [
      "CHAP",
      "TACACS+",
      "PAP",
      "RADIUS",
      "MS-CHAP"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "CHAP",
      "TACACS+",
      "RADIUS",
      "MS-CHAP"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the characteristics of TACACS+? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Encrypts only the password in the access-request packet",
      "Combines authentication and authorization",
      "Encrypts the entire payload of the access-request packet",
      "Primarily used for device administration",
      "Separates authentication and authorization",
      "Primarily used for network access"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Encrypts the entire payload of the access-request packet",
      "Separates authentication and authorization",
      "Primarily used for device administration"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the characteristic features of RADIUS? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Primarily used for network access",
      "Encrypts the entire payload of the access-request packet",
      "Combines authentication and authorization",
      "Encrypts only the password in the access-request packet",
      "Primarily used for device administration",
      "Separates authentication and authorization"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Primarily used for network access",
      "Combines authentication and authorization",
      "Encrypts only the password in the access-request packet"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following authentication protocols can be used to enable SSO in Windows-based network environments?",
    "options": [
      "PAP",
      "LDAP",
      "MS-CHAP",
      "Kerberos"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Kerberos"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],
//-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 13": [
  {
    "question": "Assigning a unique encrypted key, called a ticket, to each user that logs on to the network is a characteristic feature of:",
    "options": ["SAML", "TOTP", "RADIUS", "Kerberos"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Kerberos"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Kerberos-based authentication process, the purpose of the client's timestamp is to provide a countermeasure against:",
    "options": ["Replay attacks", "Dictionary attacks", "Birthday attacks", "Downgrade attacks"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Replay attacks"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Harmful programs used to disrupt computer operation, gather sensitive information, or gain unauthorized access to computer systems are commonly referred to as:",
    "options": ["Adware", "Malware", "Ransomware", "Spyware"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Malware"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A type of software that performs unwanted and harmful actions in disguise of a legitimate and useful program is known as a Trojan horse. This type of malware may act like a legitimate program and have all the expected functionalities, but apart from that it will also contain a portion of malicious code that the user is unaware of.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A collection of software tools used by a hacker to mask intrusion and obtain administrator-level access to a computer or computer network is known as:",
    "options": ["Rootkit", "Spyware", "Backdoor", "Trojan"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Rootkit"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the statements listed below apply to the definition of a computer virus? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "A self-replicating computer program containing malicious segment",
      "Malware that requires its host application to be run to make the virus active",
      "A standalone malicious computer program that replicates itself over a computer network",
      "Malware that can run by itself without any interaction",
      "Malicious code that attaches itself to an application program or other executable component",
      "A self-contained malicious program or code that does need a host to propagate itself"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "A self-replicating computer program containing malicious segment",
      "Malware that requires its host application to be run to make the virus active",
      "Malicious code that attaches itself to an application program or other executable component"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Malicious software collecting information about users without their knowledge/consent is called:",
    "options": ["Cryptomalware", "Adware", "Ransomware", "Spyware"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Spyware"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Malware that restricts access to a computer system by encrypting files or locking the entire system down until the user performs requested action is referred to as:",
    "options": ["Grayware", "Adware", "Ransomware", "Spyware"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Ransomware"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of spyware?",
    "options": ["Keylogger", "Vulnerability scanner", "Computer worm", "Packet sniffer"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Keylogger"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A type of virus that infects the storage drive area containing the necessary data and code used to start the OS is known as:",
    "options": ["Phage virus", "Boot sector virus", "Retrovirus", "Polymorphic virus"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Boot sector virus"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a malware type that exploits computing resources without the owner's consent?",
    "options": ["Rootkit", "Cryptominer", "Grayware", "Trojan horse"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Cryptominer"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to launch Windows Recovery Environment (WinRE) in Windows 10?",
    "options": [
      "Boot from installation media",
      "In Power menu, hold down the Shift key and select Restart",
      "Boot from Recovery Drive",
      "Perform system restart from the Settings menu",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["All of the above"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a common firewall type used for protecting a single computer? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": ["Host-based firewall", "Software firewall", "Network-based firewall", "Hardware firewall"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Host-based firewall", "Software firewall"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which firewall would provide the best protection for an ingress/egress point of a corporate network? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": ["Hardware firewall", "Network-based firewall", "Software firewall", "Host-based firewall"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Hardware firewall", "Network-based firewall"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following provides the best countermeasure against social engineering attacks?",
    "options": ["Strong passwords", "Principle of least privilege", "Implicit deny policy", "User education"],
    "correctAnswers": ["User education"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the choices listed below provides the most effective means for malware removal?",
    "options": ["Antivirus", "Anti-malware", "Software firewall", "Recovery mode", "OS reinstallation"],
    "correctAnswers": ["OS reinstallation"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A social engineering technique whereby attackers under disguise of a legitimate request attempt to gain access to confidential information is called:",
    "options": ["Phishing", "Privilege escalation", "Backdoor access", "Shoulder surfing"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Phishing"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The practice of using a telephone system to manipulate user into disclosing confidential information is known as:",
    "options": ["Whaling", "Spear phishing", "Vishing", "Pharming"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Vishing"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A situation in which an unauthorized person can view another user's display or keyboard to learn their password or other confidential information is referred to as:",
    "options": ["Spear phishing", "Tailgating", "Shoulder surfing", "Spoofing"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Shoulder surfing"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Phishing scams targeting people holding high positions in an organization or business are known as:",
    "options": ["Vishing", "Smishing", "Whaling", "Pharming"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Whaling"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is tailgating?",
    "options": [
      "Acquiring unauthorized access to confidential data",
      "Looking over someone's shoulder to get information",
      "Gaining unauthorized access to restricted areas by following another person",
      "Manipulating a user into disclosing confidential information"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Gaining unauthorized access to restricted areas by following another person"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which social engineering attack relies on identity theft?",
    "options": ["Vishing", "Impersonation", "Elicitation", "Confidential bait"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Impersonation"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In computer security, the term \"Dumpster diving\" is used to describe a practice of sifting through trash for discarded documents containing sensitive data. Found documents containing names and surnames of the employees along with the information about positions held in the company and other data can be used to facilitate social engineering attacks. Having the documents shredded or incinerated before disposal makes dumpster diving less effective and mitigates the risk of social engineering attacks.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The term \"Evil twin\" refers to a rogue Wireless Access Point (WAP) set up for eavesdropping or stealing sensitive user data. Evil twin replaces the legitimate access point and by advertising its own presence with the same SSID appears as a legitimate access point to connecting hosts.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a DoS attack?",
    "options": ["Code injection", "Resource exhaustion", "Malware infection", "Privilege escalation"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Resource exhaustion"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],
//-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 14":[
  {
    "question": "As opposed to the simple Denial of Service (DoS) attacks that usually are performed from a single system, a Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attack uses multiple compromised computer systems to perform the attack against its target. The intermediary systems that are used as a platform for the attack are the secondary victims of the DDoS attack; they are often referred to as zombies, and collectively as a botnet.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A type of attack aimed at exploiting vulnerability that is present in already released software but unknown to the software developer is called:",
    "options": ["Xmas attack", "Zero-day attack", "IV attack", "Replay attack"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Zero-day attack"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "An email sent from unknown source disguised as a trusted source known to the message receiver is an example of: (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": ["Spoofing", "Malware", "Trojan horse", "Social engineering", "On-path attack"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Spoofing", "Social engineering"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements can be used to describe the characteristics of an on-path attack? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "An on-path attack is also known as MitM attack",
      "Attackers place themselves on the communication route between two devices",
      "Attackers intercept or modify packets sent between two communicating devices",
      "An on-path attack is also known as XSS attack",
      "Attackers do not have access to packets exchanged during the communication between two devices",
      "Attackers generate forged packets and inject them in the network"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "An on-path attack is also known as MitM attack",
      "Attackers place themselves on the communication route between two devices",
      "Attackers intercept or modify packets sent between two communicating devices"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "An attack against encrypted data that relies heavily on computing power to check all possible keys and passwords until the correct one is found is referred to as:",
    "options": ["Replay attack", "Brute-force attack", "Dictionary attack", "Birthday attack"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Brute-force attack"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which password attack takes advantage of a predefined list of words?",
    "options": ["Birthday attack", "Replay attack", "Dictionary attack", "Brute-force attack"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Dictionary attack"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which term best describes a disgruntled employee abusing legitimate access to company's internal resources?",
    "options": ["APT", "Insider threat", "Gray hat", "Threat actor"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Insider threat"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Entry fields of web forms lacking input validation are vulnerable to what kind of attacks?",
    "options": ["Replay attacks", "SQL injection attacks", "Brute-force attacks", "Dictionary attacks"],
    "correctAnswers": ["SQL injection attacks"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a countermeasure against SQL injection attacks?",
    "options": ["Code obfuscation", "Database normalization", "Code signing", "Input validation"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Input validation"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers can be used to describe characteristics of an XSS attack? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Exploits the trust a user's web browser has in a website",
      "A malicious script is injected into a trusted website",
      "User's browser executes attacker's script",
      "Exploits the trust a website has in the user's web browser",
      "A user is tricked by an attacker into submitting unauthorized web requests",
      "Website executes attacker's requests"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Exploits the trust a user's web browser has in a website",
      "A malicious script is injected into a trusted website",
      "User's browser executes attacker's script"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Network Access Control (NAC) defines a set of rules enforced in a network that the clients attempting to access the network must comply with. With NAC, policies can be enforced before or after end-stations gain access to the network. NAC can be implemented as pre-admission NAC where a host must, for example, be virus free or have patches applied before it can be allowed to connect to the network, and/or post-admission NAC, where a host is being granted/denied permissions based on its actions after it has been provided with the access to the network.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A Microsoft online service used for patching up system vulnerabilities, improving system performance, and fixing coding errors found in Windows software is known as:",
    "options": ["Action Center", "Windows Update", "Security Center", "Windows Store"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Windows Update"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The basic countermeasures against application-related vulnerabilities include avoiding applications from unknown sources and keeping the already installed apps up to date with current patches and bug fixes.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A mobile device deployment model that allows employees to use private mobile devices for accessing company's restricted data and applications is called:",
    "options": ["COPE", "BYOD", "JBOD", "CYOD"],
    "correctAnswers": ["BYOD"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a potential IT security vulnerability?",
    "options": [
      "Non-compliant systems",
      "Unpatched systems",
      "Lack of security software (e.g., antivirus, firewall)",
      "OSs that got past their EOL",
      "Use of personal devices for work-related tasks",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["All of the above"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In Windows 10, Microsoft Defender Antivirus can be enabled/disabled via:",
    "options": [
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > Virus & threat protection > under Virus & threat protection settings click Manage settings > under Real-time protection switch the setting to On or Off",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > Security and Maintenance (or choose Review your computer status and resolve issues) > Security > under Virus protection select View in Windows Security > under Virus & threat protection settings click Manage settings > under Real-time protection switch the setting to On or Off",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Security and Maintenance > Security > under Virus protection select View in Windows Security > under Virus & threat protection settings click Manage settings > under Real-time protection switch the setting to On or Off",
      "Locate Windows Security icon in Windows Taskbar notification area > right-click on the icon and select View security dashboard from the pop-up menu > click Virus & threat protection > under Virus & threat protection settings click Manage settings > under Real-time protection switch the setting to On or Off",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["All of the above"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Virus definition database files contain detection patterns for known viruses. To be effective, an AV program needs up-to-date versions of these files which can be obtained through an AV software update feature.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following actions in Windows 10 provides access to virus & threat protection update setting?",
    "options": [
      "Locate Windows Security icon in Windows Taskbar notification area > right-click on the icon and select Check for protection updates from the pop-up menu",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > Security and Maintenance > Security > under Virus protection select View in Windows Security > under Virus & threat protection updates click Check for updates",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > Security and Maintenance (or choose Review your computer status and resolve issues) > Security > under Virus protection select View in Windows Security > under Virus & threat protection updates click Check for updates",
      "Windows Start > Settings > Update & Security > Windows Security > Virus & threat protection > under Virus & threat protection updates click Check for updates",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["All of the above"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an SSO account type?",
    "options": ["Guest account", "Microsoft account", "Administrator account", "Standard account"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Microsoft account"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following user groups in Windows 10 can use most software and change system settings that don't affect other users or computer's security?",
    "options": ["Guests", "Standard Users", "Power Users", "Administrators"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Standard Users"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a built-in MS Windows account with complete and unrestricted system access?",
    "options": ["root", "Power User", "Administrator", "Supervisor"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Administrator"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In MS Windows environments, Guest account is an account for users who do not have a permanent account on a Windows computer or domain. People using this type of account cannot install software or hardware, change settings, create passwords, or access protected files and folders. However, because the Guest account allows the user to log on to a network, browse the Internet, and shut down the computer, it is recommended to keep it disabled when it isn't being used.",
    "options": ["True", "False"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which user group in Windows (applies to Windows 7 and earlier versions) had rights and permissions that allowed its members to perform specific administrator-level tasks?",
    "options": ["Users", "Guests", "Power Users", "Service accounts"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Power Users"],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sign-in options in Windows 10 rely on knowledge-based authentication factors? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": ["Username", "Security Key", "PIN", "Facial recognition", "Password", "Fingerprint"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Username", "PIN", "Password"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refer to Windows 10 sign-in options that rely on inherence-based authentication factors? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": ["Fingerprint", "Facial recognition", "Password", "PIN", "Security Key", "Username"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Fingerprint", "Facial recognition"],
    "allowMultiple": true
  }
],

//------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 15":[
  {
    "question": "Which of the statements listed below are true? (Select 2 answers)\nNTFS permissions apply only to local users\nNTFS permissions can be applied only on a folder level\nNTFS permissions apply to both network and local users\nNTFS permissions can be applied to a folder or individual file",
    "options": [
      "NTFS permissions apply only to local users",
      "NTFS permissions can be applied only on a folder level",
      "NTFS permissions apply to both network and local users",
      "NTFS permissions can be applied to a folder or individual file"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "NTFS permissions apply to both network and local users",
      "NTFS permissions can be applied to a folder or individual file"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements describing share permissions in MS Windows are true? (Select 2 answers)\nApply only to network users\nCan be set on a file level\nApply to both network and local users\nCan be set on a folder level",
    "options": [
      "Apply only to network users",
      "Can be set on a file level",
      "Apply to both network and local users",
      "Can be set on a folder level"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Apply only to network users",
      "Can be set on a folder level"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "A Windows resource with conflicting NTFS and share permissions applied to it will assume:",
    "options": [
      "The least restrictive permission",
      "NTFS permissions",
      "The most restrictive permission",
      "Share permissions"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "The most restrictive permission"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The share permissions on a shared Windows folder grant the user Read access and the local NTFS permissions grant the user Modify access. Which of the following are the effective user permission levels? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Read when accessing the share remotely",
      "Modify when accessing the folder locally",
      "Read when accessing the folder locally",
      "Modify when accessing the share remotely"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Read when accessing the share remotely",
      "Modify when accessing the folder locally"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "The share permissions on a shared Windows folder grant the user Full Control access and the local NTFS permissions grant the user Read access. Which of the following are the effective user permission levels? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Read when accessing the share remotely",
      "Full control when accessing the folder locally",
      "Read when accessing the folder locally",
      "Full Control when accessing the share remotely"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Read when accessing the share remotely",
      "Read when accessing the folder locally"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct hierarchy of precedence for permissions settings in NTFS?",
    "options": [
      "Explicit Allow > Inherited Allow > Explicit Deny > Inherited Deny",
      "Explicit Deny > Explicit Allow > Inherited Deny > Inherited Allow",
      "Explicit Allow > Explicit Deny > Inherited Allow > Inherited Deny",
      "Explicit Deny > Inherited Deny > Explicit Allow > Inherited Allow"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Explicit Deny > Explicit Allow > Inherited Deny > Inherited Allow"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In MS Windows, the attrib command is used to display or change file attributes. Some of the available options for this command include read-only (R), archive (A), system (S), and hidden (H). With attrib, the '+' symbol sets an attribute for a file, the '-' sign removes the attribute.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct syntax for applying the read-only attribute to a file?",
    "options": [
      "attrib +R [drive:] [path] [filename]",
      "attrib [drive:] [path] [filename] /read-only",
      "attrib /R [drive:] [path] [filename]",
      "attrib [drive:] [path] [filename] +R"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "attrib +R [drive:] [path] [filename]"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In NTFS, permissions inherited from a parent object (e.g., a folder or user group) take precedence over permissions applied directly to an object (explicit permissions).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "False"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In NTFS, a folder or file moved from one location to another on the same volume inherits the permissions of its new parent folder.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "False"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In NTFS, a folder or file copied from one location to another on the same volume retains its original permissions.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "False"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In NTFS, a folder or file copied from one location to another on the same volume retains its original permissions.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "False"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In NTFS, permission propagation occurs when a folder or file created inside another folder takes on (inherits) permissions applied to that folder (permissions applied to the so-called parent folder propagate down to its child objects, i.e., folders and files created inside the parent folder).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The \"Run as administrator\" option in MS Windows allows users with lower-level permissions to perform tasks reserved for system administrators. This feature requires providing Administrator account credentials and temporarily elevates the current user's privileges to perform a given task. It also simplifies common system tasks, such as installation of new software, which would otherwise require logging out and switching to an admin account.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Windows Vista and newer releases of the Microsoft OS offer a security feature which limits privileges of software applications and access to administrative tasks. When a program makes a change that requires administrator-level permission or a user attempts to modify system settings that require administrative access, it triggers an on-screen prompt requiring an administrator password to proceed. This functionality is known as:",
    "options": [
      "UAC",
      "EFS",
      "TPM",
      "ACL"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "UAC"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following actions in Windows allow to invoke the user access control prompt and run an application with administrator account permissions? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Right-click on an application icon > select Run as administrator from the pop-up menu",
      "Launch Windows Run dialog box (Windows logo key + R) > type in the application's name > press Enter",
      "In Windows Start menu press and hold Control + Shift keys > left-click on an application icon",
      "Launch Windows Run dialog box (Windows logo key + R) > type in the application's name > press Control + Shift + Enter",
      "In Windows Start menu press and hold Alt + Shift keys > left-click on an application icon"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Right-click on an application icon > select Run as administrator from the pop-up menu",
      "In Windows Start menu press and hold Control + Shift keys > left-click on an application icon",
      "Launch Windows Run dialog box (Windows logo key + R) > type in the application's name > press Control + Shift + Enter"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of a Microsoft Windows feature that enables encryption of entire drives?",
    "options": [
      "FileVault",
      "DriveCrypt",
      "BitLocker",
      "TrueCrypt"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "BitLocker"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A Microsoft Windows feature specifically designed to enable encryption of removable drives is known as:",
    "options": [
      "BitLocker",
      "TrueCrypt",
      "BitLocker To Go",
      "DriveCrypt"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "BitLocker To Go"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Premium versions of the Microsoft OS contain a built-in component that enables encryption of individual files. This feature is called:",
    "options": [
      "EFS",
      "HSM",
      "AES",
      "TPM"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "EFS"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The term \"Data-at-rest encryption\" refers to the encryption process that is applied to data residing in persistent storage (e.g., internal storage drive inside computer case).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The two factors that are considered important for creating strong passwords are: (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Password length",
      "Minimum password age",
      "Password history",
      "Password complexity",
      "Maximum password age"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Password length",
      "Password complexity"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "A strong password that meets the password complexity requirement should contain: (Select the best answer)",
    "options": [
      "Uppercase letters (A-Z)",
      "Digits (0-9)",
      "Non-alphanumeric characters if permitted (e.g., !, @, #, $)",
      "Lowercase letters (a-z)",
      "A combination of characters from at least 3 character groups"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "A combination of characters from at least 3 character groups"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following password examples is the most complex?",
    "options": [
      "YzGdL3tU8wx",
      "T$7C52WL4S9@W0",
      "G$L3tU8wY@z",
      "@TxBL$nW@Xt*a#"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "T$7C52WL4S9@W0"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The importance of changing default usernames and passwords can be illustrated on the example of certain network devices (such as routers) which are often shipped with default and well-known admin credentials that can be looked up on the web.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "An account policy setting that forces users to produce a new password every time they are required to change their old password is known as:",
    "options": [
      "Password expiration",
      "Password reuse",
      "Password history",
      "Password complexity"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Password history"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],
//------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 16":[
  {
    "question": "Which of the account policy settings listed below prevents users from reusing old passwords?",
    "options": [
      "Password expiration",
      "Password history",
      "Password length",
      "Password complexity"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Password history"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which password policy setting prevents users from repeatedly changing their passwords to bypass the password history policy setting and get back to their original/preferred password?",
    "options": [
      "Minimum password age setting",
      "Password complexity setting",
      "Account lockout threshold setting",
      "Login time restrictions"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Minimum password age setting"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following password policy settings prevents attackers using cracked passwords from gaining permanent access to a Windows workstation?",
    "options": [
      "Login time restrictions",
      "Password complexity setting",
      "Account lockout threshold setting",
      "Maximum password age setting"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Account lockout threshold setting"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "BIOS/UEFI passwords improve the security of a computer host. These low-level passwords may, for example, prevent unauthorized users from proceeding when the computer is powered on (Supervisor/Administrator password), or restrict the scope of changes a user can make in the BIOS/UEFI interface (User password).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The practice of implementing a computer screen lock is one of the end-user security best practices. The screen lock can be implemented as a password-protected screensaver that activates when the computer has been idle for a specific amount of time. In MS Windows, users can manually block unauthorized access by invoking the sign-in screen with the Windows logo + L key combination whenever they're about to leave their computer desk. Screen locks can also be used as a countermeasure against brute-force attacks as they can be set to block computer access after a specified number of failed login attempts. The use of screensaver locks is an implementation of a more general security best practice which is logging off whenever the system is not in use.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In Microsoft Windows 10, screen lock settings can be accessed via:",
    "options": [
      "Settings > Personalization > Lock screen",
      "Settings > Update & Security > Lock screen",
      "Settings > System > Display > Lock screen",
      "Settings > Devices > Display settings > Lock screen"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Settings > Personalization > Lock screen"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a physical security measure against laptop theft?",
    "options": [
      "Cable lock",
      "Geotracking",
      "LoJack for Laptops",
      "Remote wipe"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Cable lock"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "USB locks are mechanical devices used for blocking a computer's USB ports from unauthorized access. USB locks can also be used to prevent the removal of an external USB device attached to the computer.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Privacy filter (a.k.a. privacy screen) is a protective overlay placed on the computer screen that narrows the viewing angle, so the screen content is only visible directly in front of the monitor and cannot be seen by others nearby. Privacy filter is one of the countermeasures against shoulder surfing.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A sticky note with a password kept on sight in user's cubicle would be a violation of which of the following policies?",
    "options": [
      "Data labeling policy",
      "Clean desk policy",
      "Acceptable Use Policy (AUP)",
      "User account policy"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Clean desk policy"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The category of account management security best practices includes the practice of restricting user administrative privileges to operating systems and applications based on user duties. Operating systems simplify this process by introducing the concept of user groups equipped with different types of permissions which allow system administrators to simultaneously manage permissions of multiple user accounts based on group membership.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following account management security measures narrows down a user's computer access to specified hours?",
    "options": [
      "Acceptable Use Policy (AUP)",
      "Job rotation policy",
      "Login time restrictions",
      "Principle of least privilege"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Login time restrictions"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Because the Guest account in MS Windows allows a user to log on to a network, browse the Internet, and shut down the computer, it is recommended to keep it disabled when it isn't being used.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which account management security solutions provide countermeasures against brute-force attacks? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Login time restrictions",
      "Timeout period between login attempts",
      "Principle of least privilege",
      "Clean desk policy",
      "Failed login attempts lockout"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Timeout period between login attempts",
      "Failed login attempts lockout"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "An MS Windows component enabling automatic execution of code contained on a newly mounted storage media is called AutoPlay.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In MS Windows, AutoRun is a system component that displays a dialog box containing applicable options for a newly mounted storage media.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "False"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sequence of steps in Windows 10 provides access to the AutoPlay settings menu? (Select 3 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > AutoPlay",
      "Settings > Devices > AutoPlay",
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > System > AutoPlay",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > AutoPlay",
      "Settings > System > AutoPlay",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > System and Security > AutoPlay"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Windows Control Panel (icon view) > AutoPlay",
      "Settings > Devices > AutoPlay",
      "Windows Control Panel (category view) > Hardware and Sound > AutoPlay"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of a user interface element controlling access to a mobile device after the device is powered on?",
    "options": [
      "Launcher",
      "Screen lock",
      "Privacy filter",
      "Hardware lock"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Screen lock"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Implementing full device encryption is one of the methods for securing sensitive data on a smartphone. When enabled, this type of encryption works in conjunction with the phone's screen lock, i.e., to decrypt the phone (which stays encrypted whenever the phone is locked), a user must first unlock the screen. On Android devices, the unlocking methods include entering a PIN, password, or drawing a simple pattern with a finger. Apple devices use passcodes, facial recognition (Face ID), and fingerprint (Touch ID).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Data on a lost or stolen mobile device can be erased by:",
    "options": [
      "Rooting",
      "Sideloading",
      "Low-level formatting",
      "Remote wipe"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Remote wipe"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A mobile device's built-in functionality enabling the usage of locator applications is called:",
    "options": [
      "WPS",
      "GSM",
      "IMEI",
      "GPS"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "GPS"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "By default, Android and iOS devices allow a limited number of failed login attempts after which the device becomes inaccessible and requires additional steps to unlock.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "An emerging field of innovative technologies, such as wearable tech or home automation is known as:",
    "options": [
      "SoC",
      "NFC",
      "IoT",
      "ESN"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "IoT"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Examples of storage media drive physical destruction methods include:",
    "options": [
      "Shredding",
      "Drilling",
      "Degaussing",
      "Incinerating",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the ways to prevent data recovery from a storage drive is to overwrite its contents. The data overwriting technique is used by drive wipe utilities which might employ different methods (including multiple overwriting rounds) to decrease the likelihood of data retrieval. As an example, a disk sanitization utility might overwrite the data on the drive with the value of one in the first pass, change that value to zero in the second pass, and finally perform five more passes, overwriting the contents with random characters (the Schneier method).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],

//-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 17":[
  {
    "question": "Which of the terms listed below is used to describe the initial storage drive formatting typically performed at the factory by the drive manufacturer?",
    "options": [
      "Low-level format",
      "Quick format",
      "Standard format",
      "High-level format"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Low-level format"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which formatting type(s) would typically be performed by a user intending to reinstall an OS? (Select all that apply)",
    "options": [
      "Quick format",
      "Low-level-format",
      "Standard format",
      "High-level format"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Quick format",
      "High-level format"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "Which format type in MS Windows does not erase disk data?",
    "options": [
      "Standard format",
      "Low-level-format",
      "High-level format",
      "Quick format"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Quick format"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which formatting type in MS Windows prevents data recovery by overwriting the contents of storage drive sectors?",
    "options": [
      "Low-level format",
      "Standard format",
      "High-level format",
      "Quick format"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "High-level format"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Certificate of destruction is a document issued by companies that conduct secure device/document disposal. The certificate verifies proper asset destruction and can be used for auditing purposes. In case of device disposal, the document includes a list of all the items that have been destroyed along with their serial numbers. It may also describe the destruction method, specify location (on-site/off-site), or list the names of witnesses who oversaw the entire process.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Because wireless routers are shipped with default credentials, the process of securing a SOHO network should include changing the default username and password on a Wireless Access Point (WAP).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of network traffic filtering criteria can be set on a router?",
    "options": [
      "Filtering by IP address",
      "Filtering by network protocol",
      "Filtering by subnet",
      "Filtering by logical port number",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a type of software embedded into a hardware chip?",
    "options": [
      "Machine code",
      "Bootloader",
      "Device driver",
      "Firmware"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Firmware"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to an application software that selectively blocks access to websites?",
    "options": [
      "Captive portal",
      "Firewall",
      "Content filter",
      "Proxy server"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Content filter"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to an example of content filtering configuration setting on a SOHO router?",
    "options": [
      "Modem mode",
      "Parental controls",
      "MAC filtering",
      "IP and port filtering"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Parental controls"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The term \"Unified Threat Management\" (UTM) refers to a network security solution, commonly in the form of a dedicated device (called UTM appliance or web security gateway), which combines the functionality of a firewall with additional features such as URL filtering, content inspection, spam filtering, gateway antivirus protection, IDS/IPS function, or malware inspection.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "An optimal Wireless Access Point (WAP) antenna placement provides a countermeasure against:",
    "options": [
      "War chalking",
      "Spoofing",
      "War driving",
      "Insider threat"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "War driving"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the WAP settings listed below allows for adjusting the boundary range of a wireless signal?",
    "options": [
      "WPS setup",
      "Radio channel",
      "Power level controls",
      "Beacon interval"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Power level controls"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following would be of help in troubleshooting wireless signal loss and low wireless network signal coverage?",
    "options": [
      "Protocol analyzer",
      "WAP power level controls",
      "Logical network diagram",
      "Network mapper"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Protocol analyzer"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A DHCP server's IP exclusion configuration option allows network administrators to remove a single IP address or a range of IP addresses from the pool of addresses being assigned automatically to the requesting DHCP client computers. IP exclusion prevents other DHCP clients from requesting an IP address statically assigned to other essential network hosts (e.g., servers, or wireless printers).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the features of DHCP is the capability for static allocation of an IP address based on the IP-to-MAC address mapping.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the terms listed below refers to permanent IP address assignment from a DHCP server?",
    "options": [
      "Scope",
      "Reservation",
      "DHCP relay",
      "Lease"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Reservation"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A permanent WAN IP address assigned to a computer by an ISP is referred to as a:",
    "options": [
      "Static IP address",
      "Private IP address",
      "Dynamic IP address",
      "Public IP address"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Static IP address"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A type of architecture that simplifies networking by allowing devices to dynamically join a network, autoconfigure, and learn about the presence and capabilities of other devices is known as:",
    "options": [
      "PoE",
      "DHCP",
      "SDN",
      "UPnP"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "UPnP"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following answers refers to the concept of zero-configuration networking?",
    "options": [
      "DHCP",
      "PnP",
      "UPnP",
      "AutoRun"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "UPnP"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Examples of technologies that should not be used due to their known vulnerabilities or other security risks include: (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "RDP",
      "UPnP",
      "WEP",
      "TLS",
      "SNMP"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "UPnP",
      "WEP"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "A lightly protected subnet (a.k.a. DMZ) consisting of publicly available servers placed on the outside of the company's firewall is called:",
    "options": [
      "Captive portal",
      "Honeynet",
      "Quarantine network",
      "Extranet",
      "Screened subnet"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Screened subnet"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Service Set Identifier (SSID) is a unique identifier (a.k.a. wireless network name) for a WLAN. Wireless networks advertise their presence by regularly broadcasting SSID in a special packet called beacon frame. In wireless networks with disabled security features, knowing the network SSID is enough to get access to the network. SSID also pinpoints the wireless router that acts as a Wireless Access Point (WAP). Wireless routers from the same manufacturer are frequently configured with default (well-known) SSID names. Since multiple devices with the same SSID displayed on the list of available networks create confusion and encourage accidental access by unauthorized users (applies to networks that lack security), changing the default SSID is a recommended practice.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Disabling SSID broadcast:",
    "options": [
      "Is one of the measures used in the process of securing wireless networks",
      "Makes a WLAN harder to discover",
      "Blocks access to a WAP",
      "Prevents wireless clients from accessing the network"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Makes a WLAN harder to discover"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "For a wireless client to be able to connect to a network, the security type (e.g., WEP, WPA, WPA2, or WPA3) and encryption type (e.g., TKIP or AES) settings on the connecting host must match the corresponding wireless security settings on a Wireless Access Point (WAP).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],

////-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ 1102 test 18": [
  {
    "question": "A type of wireless network that provides access to the Internet, but not to the internal network is referred to as guest WiFi network. Setting up a separate network for visitors (handled by a dedicated access point) protects the internal network against risks related to unauthorized activities and malware infections.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In wireless networks, channel overlapping is a situation where multiple channels share the frequency band causing interference and performance degradation for devices operating on channels that are too close to each other. A common example of channel overlapping would be the 2.4 GHz band used in 802.11 networks, where the 2.401 - 2.473 GHz frequency range is used for allocating 11 channels, each taking up a 22-MHz portion of the spectrum. Setting up a wireless network to operate on a non-overlapping channel (1, 6, and 11 in this case) allows multiple networks to coexist in the same area without causing interference.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In the context of implementing secure network designs, the term \"Port security\" may apply to:",
    "options": [
      "Disabling physical ports on a device (e.g., RJ-45 device ports on a router, switch, or patch panel)",
      "Implementing MAC filtering",
      "Disabling unused logical ports (TCP/UDP)",
      "Implementing Port-based Network Access Control (defined in the IEEE 802.1X standard)",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A server with private IP address has been set up to handle requests from an outside (public) network. Which of the solutions listed below would enable this functionality?",
    "options": [
      "Port bonding",
      "Port labeling",
      "Port forwarding",
      "Port mirroring"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Port forwarding"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Port mirroring allows an administrator to inspect traffic passing through a network switch. On a switch that supports port mirroring, a packet analyzer can be connected to an empty port and the switch can be configured to pass a copy of the data sent over one or multiple ports on that switch to the packet sniffer port allowing the administrator to monitor contents of the traffic passing through the switch.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "A hash function enables mapping large amount of data content to a small string of characters. The result of hash function provides the exact \"content in a nutshell\" (in the form of a string of alphanumeric characters) derived from the original data content. In case there is any change to the data after the original hash was taken, the next time when hash function is applied the resulting hash value calculated after content modification will be different from the original hash.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the ways of confirming that a software application comes from a trusted source is the verification of its digital signature. A digitally signed software proves the identity of the developer and guarantees that the application code has not been tampered with since it was signed. The authenticity and integrity of the application's code can be verified by comparing results of a cryptographic hash function (original hash published by the application developer vs. hash obtained from a downloaded app).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Installing web browser extensions and plug-ins from trusted sources (e.g., Microsoft Store for Microsoft Edge, or Google Play for Google Chrome) instead of third-party sites decreases malware-related security risks.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The term \"Password vault\" refers to a credential manager program that stores usernames and passwords in an encrypted form. Password vault requires a single master password for accessing a number of different passwords used for different websites or services.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Control Panel applet in Windows allows to manage usernames and passwords for websites, connected applications and networks?",
    "options": [
      "User Accounts",
      "Credential Manager",
      "Security and Maintenance",
      "Ease of Access Center"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Credential Manager"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of a network protocol that secures web traffic via SSL/TLS encryption?",
    "options": [
      "SFTP",
      "HTTPS",
      "FTPS",
      "SNMP"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "HTTPS"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following allows to check digital certificate validity?",
    "options": [
      "User Account Control (UAC) applet",
      "Web browser padlock icon menu",
      "Storage Spaces Control Panel applet",
      "Windows Security Account Manager (SAM)"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Web browser padlock icon menu"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the solutions listed below allows to check whether a digital certificate has been revoked?",
    "options": [
      "OCR",
      "CRL",
      "CSR",
      "OSPF"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "CRL"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the MS Windows utilities provides access to configuration options of a built-in pop-up blocker?",
    "options": [
      "Programs and Features (appwiz.cpl)",
      "System Configuration (msconfig.exe)",
      "Internet Properties (inetcpl.cpl)",
      "Security and Maintenance (wscui.cpl)"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Internet Properties (inetcpl.cpl)"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The term \"Web browsing data\" refers to:",
    "options": [
      "History of visited pages",
      "Downloaded files",
      "Saved passwords",
      "Cookies",
      "Web form data",
      "Cached images and files",
      "All of the above terms"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "All of the above terms"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Web caching improves:",
    "options": [
      "Privacy",
      "Data integrity",
      "Page loading speed",
      "Web browser security"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Page loading speed"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Private-browsing mode (InPrivate browsing in Microsoft Edge / Incognito mode in Google Chrome) is a privacy feature that prevents the web browser from storing data about a browsing session. Private browsing window (which can be launched with the Ctrl + Shift + N key combination) provides protection against website and ISP tracking and clears all the web browsing data associated with the session when the session is closed.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The term \"Browser synchronization\" refers to a cloud service provided by a web browser vendor for sharing browser settings and data across all web browser instances installed on devices that are signed-in to the main account (e.g., Google Account, or Microsoft account).",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "The Blue Screen of Death (BSoD) (a.k.a. stop error screen) in MS Windows indicates a fatal error that the system cannot fix on the fly to continue operate safely. BSOD provides technical information that might be of help for advanced users in solving the cause of the stop error. In older versions of Microsoft OSs, information displayed on the screen when Windows encountered this type of error typically included error code, memory address where it occurred, and the name of the driver that caused it. Starting from Windows 8, the error screen contains a stop code accompanied by a URL and QR code pointing to relevant troubleshooting resources on the Internet.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Pinwheel\" is an informal term used for describing stop error in:",
    "options": [
      "Android",
      "Linux",
      "macOS",
      "Windows"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "macOS"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "In Microsoft OSs, Performance tab in Windows Task Manager allows to identify hardware components affecting system performance. In a similar fashion, Task Manager's Processes tab can be used to identify compute-intensive applications and processes that can be the cause of sluggish system performance.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "True"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Slow computer performance may be the result of:",
    "options": [
      "Outdated system/app/driver software",
      "Insufficient amount of hardware resources (e.g., RAM)",
      "Storage drive fragmentation",
      "Depleted internal storage space",
      "System overheating",
      "Malicious software",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Slow computer performance may be the result of:",
    "options": [
      "Outdated system/app/driver software",
      "Insufficient amount of hardware resources (e.g., RAM)",
      "Storage drive fragmentation",
      "Depleted internal storage space",
      "System overheating",
      "Malicious software",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following could be of help while troubleshooting a system that attempts to boot to incorrect device? (Select 2 answers)",
    "options": [
      "Device Manager",
      "Safe mode troubleshooting",
      "Troubleshooting applet in Windows Control Panel",
      "Disconnecting any removable drives",
      "Updating boot order in BIOS"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Disconnecting any removable drives",
      "Updating boot order in BIOS"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": true
  },
  {
    "question": "During system boot, a user receives \"Windows Boot Configuration Data file is missing required information\" error message. Which of the following command-line commands should be used by a technician to troubleshoot this error?",
    "options": [
      "bootrec /scanos",
      "bootrec /rebuildbcd",
      "bootrec /fixmbr",
      "bootrec /fixboot"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "bootrec /rebuildbcd"
    ],
    "allowMultiple": false
  }
],

//------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"My questions":[
  {
    question: "How do you change an application's priority in Windows Task Manager?",
    options: [
      "Go to the Details tab, right-click the process, and select 'Set Priority'",
      "Double-click the process in the Processes tab",
      "Right-click the process in the Performance tab",
      "Use Device Manager to modify process priority"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Go to the Details tab, right-click the process, and select 'Set Priority'"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "What does the command 'tasklist /sv' do?",
    options: [
      "Lists running tasks with CPU usage details",
      "Shows a list of services running within each process",
      "Terminates specified services",
      "Displays system version information"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Shows a list of services running within each process"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following taskkill options are valid? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "/pid",
      "/im",
      "/t",
      "/£"
    ],
    // Note: The option "/£" is intentionally incorrect.
    correctAnswers: ["/pid", "/im", "/t"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which startup type in Windows delays a service's startup until after the system boots?",
    options: [
      "Automatic (Delayed)",
      "Manual",
      "Disabled",
      "Automatic"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Automatic (Delayed)"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which backup method backs up all selected data regardless of previous backups?",
    options: [
      "Full backup",
      "Incremental backup",
      "Differential backup",
      "Mirror backup"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Full backup"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following backup methods require referencing a previous backup job for data selection? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Incremental backup",
      "Differential backup",
      "Full backup",
      "Mirror backup"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Incremental backup", "Differential backup"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which OS installation types preserve user settings, applications, and data files? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Clean install",
      "In-place upgrade",
      "Repair upgrade",
      "Unattended installation"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["In-place upgrade", "Repair upgrade"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "What does running sysprep before imaging a Windows computer accomplish? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "Strips away personalization settings",
      "Removes unique system identifiers and product key",
      "Deletes all user files",
      "Resets system security identifiers (SIDs)"
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "Strips away personalization settings",
      "Removes unique system identifiers and product key",
      "Resets system security identifiers (SIDs)"
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which Windows utility is used for updating drivers and troubleshooting hardware issues?",
    options: [
      "Task Manager",
      "Device Manager",
      "Diskpart",
      "msinfo"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Device Manager"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which command-line utility is used to partition drives in Windows?",
    options: [
      "Diskpart",
      "Task Manager",
      "msinfo",
      "Device Manager"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Diskpart"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "In Unix/Linux, which command prints the current working directory?",
    options: [
      "ls",
      "cd",
      "pwd",
      "grep"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["pwd"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following commands are valid for directory traversal in Unix-like systems? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "cd",
      "chdir",
      "pwd",
      "ls"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["cd", "chdir"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following commands are used for file manipulation in Unix-like systems? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "cp",
      "mv",
      "rm",
      "grep"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["cp", "mv", "rm"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "How can you display hidden files on a Windows computer?",
    options: [
      "Open Control Panel → File Explorer Options → View tab → Show hidden files and folders",
      "Use Diskpart to list hidden files",
      "Run msinfo and filter for hidden attributes",
      "Right-click on the desktop and select 'Show hidden files'"
    ],
    correctAnswers: ["Open Control Panel → File Explorer Options → View tab → Show hidden files and folders"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following are true about the taskkill command? (Select all that apply)",
    options: [
      "It can terminate a process using its process ID with the /pid option.",
      "It can terminate a process using its image name with the /im option.",
      "It can terminate all child processes using the /t option.",
      "It lists all services running within each process."
    ],
    correctAnswers: [
      "It can terminate a process using its process ID with the /pid option.",
      "It can terminate a process using its image name with the /im option.",
      "It can terminate all child processes using the /t option."
    ],
    allowMultiple: true
  }
],

//------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
"Comptia A+ Microsoft Windows Editions": [
  {
    question: "Which Microsoft Windows 10 edition(s) provide(s) the option to join a domain? (Select all that apply)",
    options: ["Home", "Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
    correctAnswers: ["Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "In Windows 10, Assigned Access is a feature that allows to modify desktop style / user interface by restricting user account access only to a single Windows app (a.k.a. kiosk mode). Windows 10 editions offering this functionality include: (Select all that apply)",
    options: ["Windows 10 Home", "Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    // Assigned Access (kiosk mode) is not available in Home; it is available in Pro, Pro for Workstations, and Enterprise.
    correctAnswers: ["Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which edition(s) of Microsoft Windows 10 include(s) the Remote Desktop client component? (Select all that apply)",
    options: ["Home", "Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
    // Although the Remote Desktop Connection client is installed in all editions, many exam objectives note that the full client experience is emphasized in Pro and higher.
    // For exam purposes, the accepted answers are typically:
    correctAnswers: ["Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which edition of Windows 10 by default does not include the Remote Desktop server component?",
    options: ["Home", "Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
    correctAnswers: ["Home"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is the physical memory limit for all 32-bit (x86) editions of Windows 10?",
    options: ["2 GB", "4 GB", "6 GB", "8 GB"],
    correctAnswers: ["4 GB"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "A 64-bit (x64) Windows 10 Home edition provides support for up to:",
    options: ["16 GB of RAM", "32 GB of RAM", "64 GB of RAM", "128 GB of RAM"],
    correctAnswers: ["128 GB of RAM"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "What is the physical memory limit for the 64-bit (x64) Windows 10 Pro edition?",
    options: ["2 TB", "4 TB", "6 TB", "8 TB"],
    // Windows 10 Pro (64-bit) supports up to 2 TB of RAM.
    correctAnswers: ["2 TB"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the 64-bit (x64) Windows 10 editions provide(s) support for up to 6 TB of physical memory? (Select all that apply)",
    options: ["Windows 10 Home", "Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    // Only Windows 10 Pro for Workstations and Windows 10 Enterprise support up to 6 TB.
    correctAnswers: ["Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which edition(s) of Microsoft Windows 10 include(s) the BitLocker Drive Encryption feature? (Select all that apply)",
    options: ["Windows 10 Home", "Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    // BitLocker is available on Pro, Pro for Workstations, and Enterprise.
    correctAnswers: ["Windows 10 Pro", "Windows 10 Pro for Workstations", "Windows 10 Enterprise"],
    allowMultiple: true
  },
  {
    question: "Which edition of Windows 10 by default does not include the Local Group Policy Editor (gpedit.msc)?",
    options: ["Home", "Pro", "Pro for Workstations", "Enterprise"],
    correctAnswers: ["Home"],
    allowMultiple: false
  },
  {
    question: "An operating system installation type that preserves system settings, personal files, and applications from the older OS version is referred to as an in-place upgrade. Microsoft Windows versions that can be upgraded to Windows 10 via this method include: (Select 2 answers)",
    options: ["Windows XP", "Windows Vista", "Windows 7", "Windows 8.0", "Windows 8.1"],
    // In-place upgrades to Windows 10 are supported from Windows 7 and Windows 8.1.
    correctAnswers: ["Windows 7", "Windows 8.1"],
    allowMultiple: true
  }
],

//---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
    "CompTIA A+ TCP & UDP Ports": [
      {
        question: "Which port enables the FTP's Data Connection for sending file data?",
        options: ["UDP port 20", "TCP port 20", "UDP port 21", "TCP port 21"],
        correctAnswers: ["TCP port 20"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "The FTP's Control Connection for administering a session is established through:",
        options: ["TCP port 20", "UDP port 20", "TCP port 21", "UDP port 21"],
        correctAnswers: ["TCP port 21"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "SSH protocol runs on:",
        options: ["TCP port 21", "UDP port 22", "TCP port 20", "TCP port 22"],
        correctAnswers: ["TCP port 22"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the TCP ports listed below is used by Telnet?",
        options: ["20", "21", "22", "23"],
        correctAnswers: ["23"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "TCP port 25 is used by:",
        options: ["SNMP", "Telnet", "FTP", "SMTP"],
        correctAnswers: ["SMTP"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following ports is assigned to the Domain Name System (DNS)?",
        options: ["53", "67", "110", "389"],
        correctAnswers: ["53"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol (DHCP) runs on: (Select 2 answers)",
        options: ["UDP port 65", "UDP port 66", "UDP port 67", "UDP port 68", "UDP port 69"],
        correctAnswers: ["UDP port 67", "UDP port 68"],
        allowMultiple: true
      },
      {
        question: "TCP port 80 is assigned to:",
        options: ["Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP)", "Hypertext Transfer Protocol over TLS/SSL (HTTPS)", "Internet Message Access Protocol (IMAP)", "Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP)"],
        correctAnswers: ["Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP)"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "Post Office Protocol v3 (POP3) uses:",
        options: ["TCP port 110", "UDP port 123", "TCP port 143", "UDP port 161"],
        correctAnswers: ["TCP port 110"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the port numbers listed below are reserved for NetBIOS services? (Select 3 answers)",
        options: ["135", "136", "137", "138", "139"],
        correctAnswers: ["137", "138", "139"],
        allowMultiple: true
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following TCP ports is used by the Internet Message Access Protocol (IMAP)?",
        options: ["143", "389", "443", "636"],
        correctAnswers: ["143"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "An SNMP management station receives SNMP notifications from Agents on UDP port:",
        options: ["161", "137", "162", "138"],
        correctAnswers: ["162"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "An SNMP Agent receives requests on UDP port:",
        options: ["161", "137", "162", "138"],
        correctAnswers: ["161"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "TCP port 389 is the default network port for:",
        options: ["RDP", "LDAP", "SMB", "LDAPS"],
        correctAnswers: ["LDAP"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following ports is used by HTTPS?",
        options: ["TCP port 80", "TCP port 443", "UDP port 53", "TCP port 143"],
        correctAnswers: ["TCP port 443"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following protocols runs on TCP port 445?",
        options: ["HTTPS", "SMB/CIFS", "IMAP", "H.323"],
        correctAnswers: ["SMB/CIFS"],
        allowMultiple: false
      },
      {
        question: "A network technician uses Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) client on their Windows OS to remotely troubleshoot a problem on another Windows machine. Which of the following ports needs to be opened for the built-in Windows RDP server to allow this type of network connection?",
        options: ["TCP port 1720", "TCP port 636", "TCP port 3389", "TCP port 445"],
        correctAnswers: ["TCP port 3389"],
        allowMultiple: false
      }
    ],

    "Test": [
          {
            question: "Test question",
            options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
            correctAnswers: ["One"],
            allowMultiple: false
          }
      ]
    
    
  };






 
  // Utility function to shuffle an array
  export const shuffleArray = (array) => {
    const copy = [...array];
    for (let i = copy.length - 1; i > 0; i--) {
      const j = Math.floor(Math.random() * (i + 1));
      [copy[i], copy[j]] = [copy[j], copy[i]];
    }
    return copy;
  };
 
